{
	"description": "All jouyou kanji with any valid reading",
	"deck": [
	{"question":"一", "answers":[ "イチ", "イツ", "ひと", "ひとつ", "はじめ" ] },
	{"question":"乙", "answers":[ "オツ", "イツ", "おと", "きのと" ] },
	{"question":"九", "answers":[ "キュウ", "ク", "ここの", "ここのつ", "あまた" ] },
	{"question":"七", "answers":[ "シチ", "なな", "ななつ", "なの", "シツ" ] },
	{"question":"十", "answers":[ "ジッ", "ジュウ", "と", "とお", "ジュッ" ] },
	{"question":"人", "answers":[ "ジン", "ニン", "ひと" ] },
	{"question":"二", "answers":[ "ニ", "ふた", "ふたつ", "ジ" ] },
	{"question":"入", "answers":[ "ニュウ", "いる", "いれる", "はいる", "ジュ", "ジュウ", "しお" ] },
	{"question":"八", "answers":[ "ハチ", "や", "やつ", "やっつ", "よう" ] },
	{"question":"力", "answers":[ "リキ", "リョク", "ちから", "つとめる", "りきむ" ] },
	{"question":"刀", "answers":[ "トウ", "かたな" ] },
	{"question":"丁", "answers":[ "チョウ", "テイ", "トウ", "あたる", "ひのと" ] },
	{"question":"又", "answers":[ "また", "ウ", "ユウ", "ふたたび" ] },
	{"question":"了", "answers":[ "リョウ", "おわる", "さとる", "しまう" ] },
	{"question":"下", "answers":[ "カ", "ゲ", "おりる", "おろす", "くださる", "くだす", "くだる", "さがる", "さげる", "した", "しも", "もと" ] },
	{"question":"口", "answers":[ "ク", "コウ", "くち" ] },
	{"question":"三", "answers":[ "サン", "み", "みつ", "みっつ" ] },
	{"question":"山", "answers":[ "サン", "やま", "セン" ] },
	{"question":"子", "answers":[ "シ", "ス", "こ", "おとこ", "ね", "み" ] },
	{"question":"女", "answers":[ "ジョ", "おんな", "ニョ", "め", "ニョウ", "なんじ", "むすめ", "めあわせる" ] },
	{"question":"小", "answers":[ "ショウ", "お", "こ", "ちいさい", "さ" ] },
	{"question":"上", "answers":[ "ジョウ", "あがる", "あげる", "うえ", "うわ", "かみ", "のぼる", "のぼす", "のぼせる", "ショウ", "たてまつる", "ほとり" ] },
	{"question":"夕", "answers":[ "ゆう", "セキ", "ゆうべ" ] },
	{"question":"千", "answers":[ "セン", "ち" ] },
	{"question":"川", "answers":[ "かわ", "セン" ] },
	{"question":"大", "answers":[ "タイ", "ダイ", "おお", "おおいに", "おおきい", "タ", "ダ" ] },
	{"question":"土", "answers":[ "ト", "ド", "つち" ] },
	{"question":"丸", "answers":[ "ガン", "まる", "まるい", "まるめる", "たま" ] },
	{"question":"弓", "answers":[ "ゆみ", "キュウ" ] },
	{"question":"工", "answers":[ "ク", "コウ", "たくみ", "たくむ", "わざ" ] },
	{"question":"才", "answers":[ "サイ", "かど", "ざえ" ] },
	{"question":"万", "answers":[ "マン", "バン", "よろず" ] },
	{"question":"士", "answers":[ "シ", "さむらい" ] },
	{"question":"久", "answers":[ "キュウ", "ひさしい", "ク" ] },
	{"question":"干", "answers":[ "カン", "ほす", "ひる", "おかす", "かかわる", "たて", "もとめる" ] },
	{"question":"己", "answers":[ "コ", "キ", "おのれ", "つちのと" ] },
	{"question":"寸", "answers":[ "スン", "ソン", "き", "わずか" ] },
	{"question":"亡", "answers":[ "ボウ", "モウ", "ない", "ブ", "ム", "うしなう", "にげる", "ほろびる", "ほろぼす" ] },
	{"question":"及", "answers":[ "キュウ", "および", "およぶ", "およぼす" ] },
	{"question":"丈", "answers":[ "ジョウ", "たけ" ] },
	{"question":"凡", "answers":[ "ボン", "ハン", "およそ", "すべて", "なみ" ] },
	{"question":"与", "answers":[ "ヨ", "あたえる", "あずかる", "くみする" ] },
	{"question":"刃", "answers":[ "は", "ジン", "ニン", "きる", "やいば" ] },
	{"question":"巾", "answers":[ "キン", "きれ", "はば", "ふきん" ] },
	{"question":"乞", "answers":[ "こう", "キ", "キツ", "コツ" ] },
	{"question":"円", "answers":[ "エン", "まるい", "つぶらか", "まどか", "まろやか" ] },
	{"question":"王", "answers":[ "オウ", "きみ" ] },
	{"question":"火", "answers":[ "カ", "ひ", "ほ", "コ" ] },
	{"question":"月", "answers":[ "ガツ", "ゲツ", "つき" ] },
	{"question":"犬", "answers":[ "ケン", "いぬ" ] },
	{"question":"五", "answers":[ "ゴ", "いつ", "いつつ" ] },
	{"question":"手", "answers":[ "シュ", "て", "た", "ズ" ] },
	{"question":"水", "answers":[ "スイ", "みず" ] },
	{"question":"中", "answers":[ "ジュウ", "チュウ", "なか", "あたる", "あてる" ] },
	{"question":"天", "answers":[ "テン", "あま", "あめ", "そら" ] },
	{"question":"日", "answers":[ "ジツ", "ニチ", "か", "ひ" ] },
	{"question":"木", "answers":[ "ボク", "モク", "き", "こ" ] },
	{"question":"文", "answers":[ "ブン", "モン", "ふみ", "あや", "かざる" ] },
	{"question":"六", "answers":[ "ロク", "む", "むい", "むつ", "むっつ", "リク" ] },
	{"question":"引", "answers":[ "イン", "ひく", "ひける" ] },
	{"question":"牛", "answers":[ "ギュウ", "うし", "ゴ" ] },
	{"question":"今", "answers":[ "コン", "いま", "キン" ] },
	{"question":"元", "answers":[ "ガン", "ゲン", "もと", "はじめ" ] },
	{"question":"戸", "answers":[ "コ", "と", "へ" ] },
	{"question":"午", "answers":[ "ゴ", "うま", "ひる" ] },
	{"question":"公", "answers":[ "コウ", "おおやけ", "ク", "きみ" ] },
	{"question":"止", "answers":[ "シ", "とまる", "とめる", "さす", "とどまる", "とどめる", "やむ", "やめる", "よす" ] },
	{"question":"少", "answers":[ "ショウ", "すくない", "すこし", "しばらく", "まれ", "わかい" ] },
	{"question":"心", "answers":[ "シン", "こころ", "うら" ] },
	{"question":"切", "answers":[ "セツ", "きる", "きれる", "サイ" ] },
	{"question":"太", "answers":[ "タ", "タイ", "ふとい", "ふとる", "ダイ", "はなはだ" ] },
	{"question":"内", "answers":[ "ナイ", "うち", "ダイ", "ドウ", "ノウ", "いる", "いれる" ] },
	{"question":"父", "answers":[ "フ", "ちち", "ブ", "ホ" ] },
	{"question":"分", "answers":[ "ブ", "フン", "ブン", "わかつ", "わかる", "わかれる", "わける" ] },
	{"question":"方", "answers":[ "ホウ", "かた", "かく", "ただしい", "まさに" ] },
	{"question":"毛", "answers":[ "モウ", "け", "ボウ" ] },
	{"question":"友", "answers":[ "ユウ", "とも", "ウ" ] },
	{"question":"区", "answers":[ "ク", "オウ" ] },
	{"question":"化", "answers":[ "カ", "ばかす", "ばける", "ケ", "かえる", "かわる" ] },
	{"question":"反", "answers":[ "ハン", "そらす", "そる", "タン", "ホン", "かえす", "かえる", "そむく" ] },
	{"question":"予", "answers":[ "ヨ", "あたえる", "あらかじめ", "かねて", "ゆるす", "われ" ] },
	{"question":"欠", "answers":[ "ケツ", "かく", "かける", "ケン", "あくび" ] },
	{"question":"氏", "answers":[ "シ", "うじ" ] },
	{"question":"不", "answers":[ "フ", "ブ", "ず" ] },
	{"question":"夫", "answers":[ "フ", "おっと", "フウ", "ブ", "おとこ", "それ" ] },
	{"question":"支", "answers":[ "シ", "ささえる", "かう", "つかえる" ] },
	{"question":"比", "answers":[ "ヒ", "くらべる", "ビ", "ころ", "たぐい", "ならぶ" ] },
	{"question":"仏", "answers":[ "ブツ", "ほとけ", "フツ" ] },
	{"question":"尺", "answers":[ "シャク", "セキ", "さし", "ものさし", "わずか" ] },
	{"question":"収", "answers":[ "シュウ", "おさまる", "おさめる" ] },
	{"question":"仁", "answers":[ "ジン", "ニ", "ニン" ] },
	{"question":"介", "answers":[ "カイ", "すけ", "たすける" ] },
	{"question":"刈", "answers":[ "かる", "カイ", "ガイ" ] },
	{"question":"凶", "answers":[ "キョウ", "おそれる", "わざわい", "わるい" ] },
	{"question":"互", "answers":[ "ゴ", "たがい", "かたみに" ] },
	{"question":"井", "answers":[ "ショウ", "い", "セイ", "いげた" ] },
	{"question":"丹", "answers":[ "タン", "あか", "に", "まごころ" ] },
	{"question":"匹", "answers":[ "ヒツ", "ひき", "ヒキ", "たぐう" ] },
	{"question":"斤", "answers":[ "キン", "おの" ] },
	{"question":"幻", "answers":[ "ゲン", "まぼろし", "まどわす" ] },
	{"question":"孔", "answers":[ "コウ", "ク", "あな", "はなはだ" ] },
	{"question":"冗", "answers":[ "ジョウ", "むだ" ] },
	{"question":"双", "answers":[ "ソウ", "ふた", "たぐい", "ならぶ", "ふたつ", "もろ" ] },
	{"question":"斗", "answers":[ "ト", "トウ", "ひしゃく", "ます" ] },
	{"question":"乏", "answers":[ "ボウ", "とぼしい", "ホウ" ] },
	{"question":"升", "answers":[ "ショウ", "ます", "のぼる" ] },
	{"question":"弔", "answers":[ "チョウ", "とむらう" ] },
	{"question":"屯", "answers":[ "トン", "チュン", "たむろ", "なやむ" ] },
	{"question":"厄", "answers":[ "ヤク", "アク", "くるしむ", "わざわい" ] },
	{"question":"牙", "answers":[ "ゲ", "きば", "ガ", "さいとり", "は" ] },
	{"question":"勾", "answers":[ "コウ", "とらえる", "まがる" ] },
	{"question":"爪", "answers":[ "つま", "つめ", "ソウ" ] },
	{"question":"匂", "answers":[ "におう" ] },
	{"question":"片", "answers":[ "かた", "ヘン", "きれ", "ひら", "ペンス" ] },
	{"question":"玉", "answers":[ "ギョク", "たま", "ゴク" ] },
	{"question":"左", "answers":[ "サ", "ひだり" ] },
	{"question":"四", "answers":[ "シ", "よ", "よつ", "よっつ", "よん" ] },
	{"question":"出", "answers":[ "シュツ", "だす", "でる", "スイ", "いだす", "いづ" ] },
	{"question":"正", "answers":[ "ショウ", "セイ", "ただしい", "ただす", "まさ" ] },
	{"question":"生", "answers":[ "ショウ", "セイ", "いかす", "いきる", "いける", "うまれる", "うむ", "なま", "はえる", "はやす", "おう", "き", "いのち", "うぶ", "なす", "なる" ] },
	{"question":"石", "answers":[ "シャク", "セキ", "いし", "コク", "ジャク" ] },
	{"question":"田", "answers":[ "デン", "た", "かり", "かる" ] },
	{"question":"白", "answers":[ "ハク", "しら", "しろ", "しろい", "ビャク", "あきらか", "せりふ", "もうす" ] },
	{"question":"本", "answers":[ "ホン", "もと" ] },
	{"question":"目", "answers":[ "モク", "め", "ボク", "ま", "かなめ", "まなこ" ] },
	{"question":"右", "answers":[ "ウ", "ユウ", "みぎ", "たすける" ] },
	{"question":"立", "answers":[ "リツ", "たつ", "たてる", "リュウ", "リットル" ] },
	{"question":"外", "answers":[ "ガイ", "そと", "はずす", "はずれる", "ほか", "ゲ", "ウイ", "と" ] },
	{"question":"兄", "answers":[ "キョウ", "あに", "ケイ", "え" ] },
	{"question":"古", "answers":[ "コ", "ふるい", "ふるす", "いにしえ" ] },
	{"question":"広", "answers":[ "コウ", "ひろい", "ひろがる", "ひろげる", "ひろまる", "ひろめる" ] },
	{"question":"矢", "answers":[ "や", "シ" ] },
	{"question":"市", "answers":[ "シ", "いち" ] },
	{"question":"台", "answers":[ "タイ", "ダイ", "イ", "うてな", "しもべ" ] },
	{"question":"冬", "answers":[ "トウ", "ふゆ" ] },
	{"question":"半", "answers":[ "ハン", "なかば" ] },
	{"question":"母", "answers":[ "ボ", "はは", "ボウ", "モ" ] },
	{"question":"北", "answers":[ "ホク", "きた", "ハイ", "そむく", "にげる" ] },
	{"question":"用", "answers":[ "ヨウ", "もちいる", "はたらき", "もって" ] },
	{"question":"央", "answers":[ "オウ", "エイ", "ヨウ", "なかば" ] },
	{"question":"去", "answers":[ "キョ", "コ", "さる", "のぞく", "ゆく" ] },
	{"question":"号", "answers":[ "ゴウ", "コウ", "さけぶ", "よびな" ] },
	{"question":"皿", "answers":[ "さら", "ベイ" ] },
	{"question":"仕", "answers":[ "シ", "つかえる", "ジ", "つかまつる" ] },
	{"question":"写", "answers":[ "シャ", "うつす", "うつる" ] },
	{"question":"主", "answers":[ "シュ", "おも", "ぬし", "ス", "あるじ", "つかさどる" ] },
	{"question":"申", "answers":[ "もうす", "シン", "かさねる", "さる" ] },
	{"question":"世", "answers":[ "セ", "セイ", "よ" ] },
	{"question":"他", "answers":[ "タ", "ほか" ] },
	{"question":"打", "answers":[ "ダ", "うつ", "チョウ", "テイ", "ダス", "ぶつ" ] },
	{"question":"代", "answers":[ "タイ", "ダイ", "かえる", "かわる", "よ", "しろ" ] },
	{"question":"皮", "answers":[ "ヒ", "かわ" ] },
	{"question":"氷", "answers":[ "ヒョウ", "こおり", "ひ", "こおる" ] },
	{"question":"平", "answers":[ "ビョウ", "ヘイ", "たいら", "ヒョウ", "ヘン" ] },
	{"question":"由", "answers":[ "ユ", "ユウ", "ユイ", "よし", "なお", "よる" ] },
	{"question":"礼", "answers":[ "レイ", "ライ", "うやまう", "のり" ] },
	{"question":"以", "answers":[ "イ", "もちいる", "もって" ] },
	{"question":"加", "answers":[ "カ", "くわえる", "くわわる" ] },
	{"question":"功", "answers":[ "コウ", "ク", "いさお" ] },
	{"question":"札", "answers":[ "サツ", "ふだ", "さね", "わかじに" ] },
	{"question":"史", "answers":[ "シ", "ふびと", "ふみ" ] },
	{"question":"司", "answers":[ "シ", "ス", "つかさ", "つかさどる" ] },
	{"question":"失", "answers":[ "シツ", "うしなう", "イツ", "うせる" ] },
	{"question":"必", "answers":[ "ヒツ", "かならず" ] },
	{"question":"付", "answers":[ "フ", "つく", "つける", "あたえる" ] },
	{"question":"辺", "answers":[ "ヘン", "あたり", "べ", "ほとり" ] },
	{"question":"包", "answers":[ "ホウ", "つつむ", "くるむ" ] },
	{"question":"末", "answers":[ "マツ", "すえ", "バツ", "うら" ] },
	{"question":"未", "answers":[ "ミ", "ビ", "いまだ", "ひつじ", "まだ" ] },
	{"question":"民", "answers":[ "ミン", "たみ" ] },
	{"question":"令", "answers":[ "レイ", "リョウ", "いいつけ", "おさ", "よい" ] },
	{"question":"圧", "answers":[ "アツ", "オウ", "おさえる", "おす", "へす" ] },
	{"question":"永", "answers":[ "エイ", "ながい", "ヨウ", "とこしえ" ] },
	{"question":"可", "answers":[ "カ", "コク", "べし", "よい" ] },
	{"question":"刊", "answers":[ "カン", "きざむ", "けずる" ] },
	{"question":"旧", "answers":[ "キュウ", "ふる", "ふるい", "ふるびる", "もと" ] },
	{"question":"句", "answers":[ "ク", "コウ", "あたる", "まがる" ] },
	{"question":"示", "answers":[ "ジ", "しめす", "シ", "キ", "ギ" ] },
	{"question":"犯", "answers":[ "ハン", "おかす", "ボン" ] },
	{"question":"布", "answers":[ "フ", "ぬの", "ホ", "しく" ] },
	{"question":"弁", "answers":[ "ベン", "かたる", "かんむり", "とく", "はなびら", "わきまえる", "わける" ] },
	{"question":"穴", "answers":[ "あな", "ケツ" ] },
	{"question":"冊", "answers":[ "サツ", "サク", "たてる", "ふみ" ] },
	{"question":"処", "answers":[ "ショ", "ソ", "おく", "おる", "ところ" ] },
	{"question":"庁", "answers":[ "チョウ", "テイ" ] },
	{"question":"幼", "answers":[ "ヨウ", "おさない", "ユウ", "いとけない" ] },
	{"question":"甘", "answers":[ "カン", "あまい", "あまえる", "あまやかす", "うまい" ] },
	{"question":"丘", "answers":[ "キュウ", "おか" ] },
	{"question":"巨", "answers":[ "キョ", "コ", "おおい", "おおきい" ] },
	{"question":"玄", "answers":[ "ゲン", "くろ", "くろい" ] },
	{"question":"込", "answers":[ "こむ", "こめる" ] },
	{"question":"召", "answers":[ "ショウ", "めす" ] },
	{"question":"占", "answers":[ "セン", "うらなう", "しめる" ] },
	{"question":"奴", "answers":[ "ド", "ヌ", "め", "やつ", "やっこ" ] },
	{"question":"払", "answers":[ "はらう", "フツ", "ヒツ" ] },
	{"question":"矛", "answers":[ "ム", "ほこ", "ボウ" ] },
	{"question":"甲", "answers":[ "カン", "コウ", "かぶと", "きのえ", "つめ", "よろい" ] },
	{"question":"巧", "answers":[ "コウ", "たくみ", "うまい", "たくむ" ] },
	{"question":"斥", "answers":[ "セキ", "うかがう", "しりぞける" ] },
	{"question":"凹", "answers":[ "オウ", "くぼむ", "へこます", "へこむ" ] },
	{"question":"且", "answers":[ "かつ", "ショ", "しばらく", "まさに" ] },
	{"question":"囚", "answers":[ "シュウ", "とらえる", "とらわれる" ] },
	{"question":"汁", "answers":[ "ジュウ", "しる", "シュウ", "つゆ" ] },
	{"question":"仙", "answers":[ "セン" ] },
	{"question":"凸", "answers":[ "トツ", "でこ" ] },
	{"question":"尼", "answers":[ "あま", "ニ", "ジ" ] },
	{"question":"丙", "answers":[ "ヘイ", "ひのえ" ] },
	{"question":"瓦", "answers":[ "かわら", "ガ", "かわらけ", "グラム" ] },
	{"question":"叱", "answers":[ "シツ", "しかる", "シチ" ] },
	{"question":"尻", "answers":[ "しり", "コウ", "けつ" ] },
	{"question":"旦", "answers":[ "タン", "ダン", "あした" ] },
	{"question":"丼", "answers":[ "どん", "どんぶり", "セイ", "ショウ", "タン", "トン" ] },
	{"question":"氾", "answers":[ "ハン", "あふれる", "ひろがる" ] },
	{"question":"休", "answers":[ "キュウ", "やすまる", "やすむ", "やすめる", "ク", "いこう", "さいわい", "やめる", "よい" ] },
	{"question":"気", "answers":[ "キ", "ケ", "いき" ] },
	{"question":"糸", "answers":[ "シ", "いと", "ベキ" ] },
	{"question":"字", "answers":[ "ジ", "あざ", "シ", "あざな" ] },
	{"question":"耳", "answers":[ "みみ", "ジ", "ニ", "のみ" ] },
	{"question":"先", "answers":[ "セン", "さき", "まず" ] },
	{"question":"早", "answers":[ "ソウ", "はやい", "はやまる", "はやめる", "サッ", "さ" ] },
	{"question":"竹", "answers":[ "チク", "たけ", "シツ" ] },
	{"question":"虫", "answers":[ "チュウ", "むし", "キ" ] },
	{"question":"年", "answers":[ "ネン", "とし", "デン", "とせ", "みのり", "よわい" ] },
	{"question":"百", "answers":[ "ヒャク", "ハク", "もも" ] },
	{"question":"名", "answers":[ "ミョウ", "メイ", "な" ] },
	{"question":"羽", "answers":[ "は", "はね", "ウ" ] },
	{"question":"会", "answers":[ "カイ", "あう", "エ", "あつまる", "あつめる" ] },
	{"question":"回", "answers":[ "カイ", "まわす", "まわる", "エ", "めぐらす", "めぐる" ] },
	{"question":"交", "answers":[ "コウ", "まざる", "まじえる", "まじる", "まじわる", "まぜる", "かう", "かわす", "こもごも" ] },
	{"question":"光", "answers":[ "コウ", "ひかり", "ひかる" ] },
	{"question":"考", "answers":[ "コウ", "かんがえる" ] },
	{"question":"行", "answers":[ "ギョウ", "コウ", "いく", "おこなう", "ゆく", "アン", "しぬ", "みち", "やる" ] },
	{"question":"合", "answers":[ "カッ", "ガッ", "ゴウ", "あう", "あわす", "あわせる", "コウ" ] },
	{"question":"寺", "answers":[ "ジ", "てら" ] },
	{"question":"自", "answers":[ "シ", "ジ", "みずから", "おのずから", "より" ] },
	{"question":"色", "answers":[ "シキ", "ショク", "いろ" ] },
	{"question":"西", "answers":[ "サイ", "セイ", "にし", "スイ" ] },
	{"question":"多", "answers":[ "タ", "おおい" ] },
	{"question":"池", "answers":[ "チ", "いけ" ] },
	{"question":"地", "answers":[ "ジ", "チ", "つち", "ところ" ] },
	{"question":"当", "answers":[ "トウ", "あたる", "あてる", "まさに" ] },
	{"question":"同", "answers":[ "ドウ", "おなじ", "トウ", "ともに" ] },
	{"question":"肉", "answers":[ "ニク", "ジク", "しし" ] },
	{"question":"米", "answers":[ "ベイ", "マイ", "こめ", "メ", "メトル", "よね" ] },
	{"question":"毎", "answers":[ "マイ", "バイ", "ごと", "つね", "むさぼる" ] },
	{"question":"安", "answers":[ "アン", "やすい", "いずくんぞ", "やすんじる" ] },
	{"question":"曲", "answers":[ "キョク", "まがる", "まげる", "かね", "くせ", "くま", "まが" ] },
	{"question":"血", "answers":[ "ケツ", "ち", "ケチ" ] },
	{"question":"向", "answers":[ "コウ", "むかう", "むく", "むける", "むこう", "キョウ", "ショウ", "さきに" ] },
	{"question":"死", "answers":[ "シ", "しぬ" ] },
	{"question":"次", "answers":[ "ジ", "つぎ", "つぐ", "シ", "ついず", "やどる" ] },
	{"question":"式", "answers":[ "シキ", "ショク", "のっとる", "のり" ] },
	{"question":"守", "answers":[ "シュ", "ス", "まもる", "もり", "かみ" ] },
	{"question":"州", "answers":[ "シュウ", "す", "ス", "くに", "しま" ] },
	{"question":"全", "answers":[ "ゼン", "すべて", "まったく", "セン" ] },
	{"question":"有", "answers":[ "ユウ", "ある", "ウ", "もつ" ] },
	{"question":"羊", "answers":[ "ヨウ", "ひつじ" ] },
	{"question":"両", "answers":[ "リョウ", "ふたつ" ] },
	{"question":"列", "answers":[ "レツ", "つらなる", "つらねる", "ならべる" ] },
	{"question":"衣", "answers":[ "イ", "ころも", "エ", "きぬ", "きる" ] },
	{"question":"印", "answers":[ "イン", "しるし", "しるす" ] },
	{"question":"各", "answers":[ "カク", "おのおの" ] },
	{"question":"共", "answers":[ "キョウ", "とも" ] },
	{"question":"好", "answers":[ "コウ", "このむ", "すく", "よい", "よしみ" ] },
	{"question":"成", "answers":[ "セイ", "なす", "なる", "ジョウ" ] },
	{"question":"争", "answers":[ "ソウ", "あらそう", "いさめる" ] },
	{"question":"仲", "answers":[ "なか", "チュウ" ] },
	{"question":"兆", "answers":[ "チョウ", "きざし", "きざす", "ジョウ", "うらない" ] },
	{"question":"伝", "answers":[ "デン", "つたう", "つたえる", "つたわる", "テン", "つて" ] },
	{"question":"灯", "answers":[ "トウ", "ひ", "チョウ", "チン", "テイ", "ドン", "あかし", "あかり", "とぼし", "とぼす", "ともし", "ともしび", "ともす", "ともる" ] },
	{"question":"老", "answers":[ "ロウ", "おいる", "ふける" ] },
	{"question":"因", "answers":[ "イン", "よる", "ちなみ", "ちなむ", "よすが", "よって" ] },
	{"question":"仮", "answers":[ "カ", "かり", "ケ", "カク", "かす" ] },
	{"question":"件", "answers":[ "ケン", "くだり", "くだん" ] },
	{"question":"再", "answers":[ "サ", "サイ", "ふたたび" ] },
	{"question":"在", "answers":[ "ザイ", "ある", "います", "まします" ] },
	{"question":"舌", "answers":[ "した", "ゼツ", "セツ", "ことば" ] },
	{"question":"団", "answers":[ "ダン", "トン", "タン", "かたまり", "まるい" ] },
	{"question":"任", "answers":[ "ニン", "まかす", "まかせる", "ジン" ] },
	{"question":"宇", "answers":[ "ウ", "いえ", "のき" ] },
	{"question":"灰", "answers":[ "はい", "カイ", "ケ" ] },
	{"question":"危", "answers":[ "キ", "あぶない", "あやうい", "あやぶむ", "あやめる", "たかい" ] },
	{"question":"机", "answers":[ "つくえ", "キ" ] },
	{"question":"吸", "answers":[ "キュウ", "すう" ] },
	{"question":"后", "answers":[ "コウ", "ゴ", "きさき", "きみ", "のち" ] },
	{"question":"至", "answers":[ "シ", "いたる" ] },
	{"question":"存", "answers":[ "ソン", "ゾン", "ある", "たもつ", "とう", "ながらえる" ] },
	{"question":"宅", "answers":[ "タク", "いえ", "やけ" ] },
	{"question":"扱", "answers":[ "あつかう", "キュウ", "ソウ", "こく", "しごく" ] },
	{"question":"芋", "answers":[ "いも", "ウ" ] },
	{"question":"汚", "answers":[ "オ", "きたない", "よごす", "よごれる", "けがす", "けがらわしい", "けがれる" ] },
	{"question":"汗", "answers":[ "カン", "あせ" ] },
	{"question":"朽", "answers":[ "キュウ", "くちる", "すたれる" ] },
	{"question":"叫", "answers":[ "キョウ", "さけぶ" ] },
	{"question":"仰", "answers":[ "ギョウ", "コウ", "あおぐ", "おおせ", "ゴウ", "あおのく", "のく" ] },
	{"question":"旨", "answers":[ "シ", "むね", "うまい" ] },
	{"question":"芝", "answers":[ "しば", "シ" ] },
	{"question":"朱", "answers":[ "シュ", "ス", "あか", "あかい", "あけ" ] },
	{"question":"舟", "answers":[ "シュウ", "ふな", "ふね", "シュ" ] },
	{"question":"巡", "answers":[ "ジュン", "めぐる", "まわる" ] },
	{"question":"旬", "answers":[ "シュン", "ジュン" ] },
	{"question":"尽", "answers":[ "ジン", "つかす", "つきる", "つくす", "ことごとく", "すがれる" ] },
	{"question":"吐", "answers":[ "ト", "はく", "つく", "ぬかす" ] },
	{"question":"弐", "answers":[ "ニ", "ジ", "ふた", "ふたつ" ] },
	{"question":"忙", "answers":[ "ボウ", "いそがしい", "モウ", "せわしい" ] },
	{"question":"劣", "answers":[ "レツ", "おとる", "いやしい" ] },
	{"question":"企", "answers":[ "キ", "くわだてる", "たくらむ" ] },
	{"question":"吉", "answers":[ "キチ", "キツ", "よい" ] },
	{"question":"刑", "answers":[ "ケイ", "ギョウ", "しおき", "のり" ] },
	{"question":"如", "answers":[ "ジョ", "ニョ", "ごとし", "しく", "もし", "ゆく" ] },
	{"question":"匠", "answers":[ "ショウ", "たくみ" ] },
	{"question":"伐", "answers":[ "バツ", "ハツ", "うつ", "きる", "ほこる" ] },
	{"question":"帆", "answers":[ "ハン", "ほ" ] },
	{"question":"伏", "answers":[ "フク", "ふす", "ふせる", "ブク", "かくれる", "したがう" ] },
	{"question":"吏", "answers":[ "リ", "つかさ" ] },
	{"question":"缶", "answers":[ "カン", "フ", "かま", "ほとぎ" ] },
	{"question":"江", "answers":[ "コウ", "え" ] },
	{"question":"充", "answers":[ "ジュウ", "あてる", "シュウ", "みたす", "みちる", "みつ" ] },
	{"question":"迅", "answers":[ "ジン", "はげしい", "はやい" ] },
	{"question":"壮", "answers":[ "ソウ", "さかん" ] },
	{"question":"肌", "answers":[ "はだ", "キ", "はだえ" ] },
	{"question":"妃", "answers":[ "ヒ", "ハイ", "きさき" ] },
	{"question":"朴", "answers":[ "ボク", "ハク", "えのき", "すなお", "ほお" ] },
	{"question":"妄", "answers":[ "モウ", "ボウ", "みだりに" ] },
	{"question":"伎", "answers":[ "キ", "ギ", "たくみ", "わざ" ] },
	{"question":"臼", "answers":[ "キュウ", "うす" ] },
	{"question":"汎", "answers":[ "ハン", "フウ", "ホウ", "あふれる", "うかぶ", "ひろい" ] },
	{"question":"花", "answers":[ "カ", "はな", "ケ" ] },
	{"question":"貝", "answers":[ "かい", "バイ" ] },
	{"question":"見", "answers":[ "ケン", "みえる", "みせる", "みる", "ゲン", "あらわす", "あらわれる", "まみえる" ] },
	{"question":"車", "answers":[ "シャ", "くるま" ] },
	{"question":"赤", "answers":[ "セキ", "あか", "あかい", "あからむ", "あからめる", "シャク" ] },
	{"question":"足", "answers":[ "ソク", "あし", "たす", "たりる", "たる" ] },
	{"question":"村", "answers":[ "ソン", "むら" ] },
	{"question":"男", "answers":[ "ダン", "ナン", "おとこ", "おのこ" ] },
	{"question":"町", "answers":[ "チョウ", "まち", "テイ", "あぜみち" ] },
	{"question":"何", "answers":[ "なに", "なん", "カ", "いずく", "いずれ" ] },
	{"question":"角", "answers":[ "カク", "かど", "つの", "ロク", "くらべる", "すみ" ] },
	{"question":"汽", "answers":[ "キ", "ゆげ" ] },
	{"question":"近", "answers":[ "キン", "ちかい", "コン" ] },
	{"question":"形", "answers":[ "ギョウ", "ケイ", "かた", "かたち", "なり" ] },
	{"question":"言", "answers":[ "ゲン", "ゴン", "いう", "こと", "ギン", "ことば" ] },
	{"question":"谷", "answers":[ "たに", "コク", "ロク", "きわまる", "や" ] },
	{"question":"作", "answers":[ "サ", "サク", "つくる", "なす" ] },
	{"question":"社", "answers":[ "シャ", "やしろ", "ジャ" ] },
	{"question":"図", "answers":[ "ズ", "ト", "はかる", "え" ] },
	{"question":"声", "answers":[ "セイ", "こえ", "こわ", "ショウ" ] },
	{"question":"走", "answers":[ "ソウ", "はしる" ] },
	{"question":"体", "answers":[ "タイ", "からだ", "テイ" ] },
	{"question":"弟", "answers":[ "ダイ", "おとうと", "デ", "テイ" ] },
	{"question":"売", "answers":[ "バイ", "うる", "うれる" ] },
	{"question":"麦", "answers":[ "むぎ", "バク" ] },
	{"question":"来", "answers":[ "ライ", "くる", "きたす", "きたる", "きし", "こし" ] },
	{"question":"里", "answers":[ "リ", "さと" ] },
	{"question":"医", "answers":[ "イ", "いやす", "くすし" ] },
	{"question":"究", "answers":[ "キュウ", "きわめる", "ク", "きわまる" ] },
	{"question":"局", "answers":[ "キョク", "つぼね" ] },
	{"question":"君", "answers":[ "クン", "きみ" ] },
	{"question":"決", "answers":[ "ケツ", "きまる", "きめる" ] },
	{"question":"住", "answers":[ "ジュウ", "すまう", "すむ", "チュウ", "とどまる" ] },
	{"question":"助", "answers":[ "ジョ", "たすかる", "たすける", "すけ" ] },
	{"question":"身", "answers":[ "シン", "み", "みずから" ] },
	{"question":"対", "answers":[ "タイ", "ツイ", "こたえる", "そろい", "つれあい", "むかう" ] },
	{"question":"投", "answers":[ "トウ", "なげる" ] },
	{"question":"豆", "answers":[ "ズ", "トウ", "まめ", "たかつき" ] },
	{"question":"坂", "answers":[ "さか", "ハン", "バン" ] },
	{"question":"返", "answers":[ "ヘン", "かえす", "かえる", "ハン", "ホン" ] },
	{"question":"役", "answers":[ "ヤク", "エキ", "いくさ", "つとめ" ] },
	{"question":"位", "answers":[ "イ", "くらい" ] },
	{"question":"囲", "answers":[ "イ", "かこう", "かこむ" ] },
	{"question":"改", "answers":[ "カイ", "あらたまる", "あらためる" ] },
	{"question":"完", "answers":[ "カン", "まっとうする" ] },
	{"question":"希", "answers":[ "キ", "ケ", "こいねがう", "まれ" ] },
	{"question":"求", "answers":[ "キュウ", "もとめる", "グ" ] },
	{"question":"芸", "answers":[ "ゲイ", "ウン", "うえる", "くさぎる", "わざ" ] },
	{"question":"告", "answers":[ "コク", "つげる", "コウ" ] },
	{"question":"材", "answers":[ "ザイ", "サイ", "まるた" ] },
	{"question":"児", "answers":[ "ジ", "ニ", "こ" ] },
	{"question":"初", "answers":[ "ショ", "はじめ", "はじめて", "はつ", "そめる", "うい", "ソ", "うぶ" ] },
	{"question":"臣", "answers":[ "シン", "ジン", "おみ" ] },
	{"question":"折", "answers":[ "セツ", "おり", "おる", "おれる", "シャク", "くじける", "さだめる" ] },
	{"question":"束", "answers":[ "ソク", "たば", "つか", "つかねる" ] },
	{"question":"低", "answers":[ "テイ", "ひくい", "ひくまる", "ひくめる", "たれる" ] },
	{"question":"努", "answers":[ "ド", "つとめる", "ゆめ" ] },
	{"question":"兵", "answers":[ "ヘイ", "ヒョウ", "いくさ", "つわもの" ] },
	{"question":"別", "answers":[ "ベツ", "わかれる", "ベチ", "わかつ", "わける" ] },
	{"question":"利", "answers":[ "リ", "きく", "するどい", "とし", "よい" ] },
	{"question":"良", "answers":[ "リョウ", "よい", "やや" ] },
	{"question":"冷", "answers":[ "レイ", "さます", "さめる", "つめたい", "ひえる", "ひや", "ひやかす", "ひやす" ] },
	{"question":"労", "answers":[ "ロウ", "いたわる", "つかれる", "ねぎらう", "はたらく" ] },
	{"question":"応", "answers":[ "オウ", "こたえる", "まさに" ] },
	{"question":"快", "answers":[ "カイ", "こころよい", "ケ" ] },
	{"question":"技", "answers":[ "ギ", "わざ" ] },
	{"question":"均", "answers":[ "キン", "イン", "ウン", "ととのえる", "ならす", "ひとしい" ] },
	{"question":"災", "answers":[ "サイ", "わざわい" ] },
	{"question":"志", "answers":[ "シ", "こころざし", "こころざす", "しるす" ] },
	{"question":"似", "answers":[ "にる", "ジ", "シ", "ごとし" ] },
	{"question":"序", "answers":[ "ジョ", "ついで", "はしがき", "まなびや" ] },
	{"question":"状", "answers":[ "ジョウ", "かきつけ", "かたち" ] },
	{"question":"条", "answers":[ "ジョウ", "えだ", "すじ" ] },
	{"question":"判", "answers":[ "ハン", "バン", "ホウ", "わかる", "わける" ] },
	{"question":"防", "answers":[ "ボウ", "ふせぐ", "ホウ", "まもる" ] },
	{"question":"余", "answers":[ "ヨ", "あます", "あまる", "ほか", "われ" ] },
	{"question":"我", "answers":[ "われ", "ガ", "わ" ] },
	{"question":"系", "answers":[ "ケイ", "すじ", "つなぐ" ] },
	{"question":"孝", "answers":[ "コウ", "キョウ" ] },
	{"question":"困", "answers":[ "コン", "こまる", "くるしむ" ] },
	{"question":"私", "answers":[ "シ", "わたくし", "わたし", "ひそか" ] },
	{"question":"否", "answers":[ "ヒ", "いな", "フ", "いや", "わるい" ] },
	{"question":"批", "answers":[ "ヒ", "うつ", "ただす" ] },
	{"question":"忘", "answers":[ "わすれる", "ボウ", "モウ" ] },
	{"question":"卵", "answers":[ "たまご", "ラン" ] },
	{"question":"乱", "answers":[ "ラン", "みだす", "みだれる", "ロン", "みだりに" ] },
	{"question":"壱", "answers":[ "イチ", "イツ", "ひとつ" ] },
	{"question":"戒", "answers":[ "カイ", "いましめる" ] },
	{"question":"含", "answers":[ "ガン", "ふくむ", "ふくめる", "カン", "ゴン" ] },
	{"question":"却", "answers":[ "キャク", "かえって", "しりぞく", "しりぞける" ] },
	{"question":"狂", "answers":[ "キョウ", "くるう", "くるおしい", "ふれる" ] },
	{"question":"迎", "answers":[ "ゲイ", "むかえる", "ギョウ", "ゴウ" ] },
	{"question":"更", "answers":[ "コウ", "さら", "ふかす", "ふける", "あらためる", "かえる" ] },
	{"question":"抗", "answers":[ "コウ", "あらがう", "こばむ", "はりあう", "ふせぐ" ] },
	{"question":"攻", "answers":[ "コウ", "せめる", "おさめる", "みがく" ] },
	{"question":"伺", "answers":[ "うかがう", "シ" ] },
	{"question":"秀", "answers":[ "シュウ", "ひいでる" ] },
	{"question":"床", "answers":[ "ショウ", "とこ", "ゆか" ] },
	{"question":"吹", "answers":[ "スイ", "ふく" ] },
	{"question":"即", "answers":[ "ソク", "ショク", "すなわち", "つく" ] },
	{"question":"沢", "answers":[ "タク", "さわ", "うるおう", "つや" ] },
	{"question":"沖", "answers":[ "おき", "チュウ", "とぶ", "むなしい" ] },
	{"question":"沈", "answers":[ "チン", "しずむ", "しずめる", "ジン" ] },
	{"question":"抜", "answers":[ "バツ", "ぬかす", "ぬかる", "ぬく", "ぬける" ] },
	{"question":"尾", "answers":[ "ビ", "お" ] },
	{"question":"坊", "answers":[ "ボウ", "ボッ", "ホウ", "へや", "まち" ] },
	{"question":"妙", "answers":[ "ミョウ", "ビョウ", "たえ", "わかい" ] },
	{"question":"肝", "answers":[ "カン", "きも" ] },
	{"question":"忌", "answers":[ "キ", "いまわしい", "いむ" ] },
	{"question":"岐", "answers":[ "キ", "ギ", "ちまた", "わかれる" ] },
	{"question":"坑", "answers":[ "コウ", "あな" ] },
	{"question":"克", "answers":[ "コク", "かつ", "よく" ] },
	{"question":"寿", "answers":[ "ジュ", "ことぶき", "ス", "いのちながし", "ことほぐ", "とし", "ひさしい" ] },
	{"question":"伸", "answers":[ "シン", "のばす", "のびる", "のべる", "のす", "のる" ] },
	{"question":"辛", "answers":[ "シン", "からい", "かのと", "つらい" ] },
	{"question":"択", "answers":[ "タク", "えらぶ", "よる" ] },
	{"question":"尿", "answers":[ "ニョウ", "いばり", "しと", "ゆばり" ] },
	{"question":"伴", "answers":[ "ハン", "バン", "ともなう", "とも" ] },
	{"question":"芳", "answers":[ "ホウ", "かんばしい", "かおり", "かぐわしい" ] },
	{"question":"邦", "answers":[ "ホウ", "くに" ] },
	{"question":"妨", "answers":[ "ボウ", "さまたげる", "ホウ" ] },
	{"question":"没", "answers":[ "ボツ", "モツ", "おぼれる", "しずむ", "しぬ", "ない" ] },
	{"question":"抑", "answers":[ "ヨク", "おさえる", "そもそも", "ふさぐ" ] },
	{"question":"励", "answers":[ "レイ", "はげます", "はげむ" ] },
	{"question":"亜", "answers":[ "ア", "つぐ" ] },
	{"question":"吟", "answers":[ "ギン", "うたう", "うめく" ] },
	{"question":"呉", "answers":[ "ゴ", "くれ", "くれる" ] },
	{"question":"佐", "answers":[ "サ", "すけ", "たすける" ] },
	{"question":"肖", "answers":[ "ショウ", "あやかる", "かたどる", "にる" ] },
	{"question":"抄", "answers":[ "ショウ", "ソウ", "うつす", "かすめる", "すく", "すくう" ] },
	{"question":"杉", "answers":[ "すぎ", "サン" ] },
	{"question":"妥", "answers":[ "ダ", "タ", "おだやか", "やすらか" ] },
	{"question":"但", "answers":[ "ただし", "タン", "ダン", "ただ" ] },
	{"question":"呈", "answers":[ "テイ", "しめす" ] },
	{"question":"廷", "answers":[ "テイ", "にわ" ] },
	{"question":"忍", "answers":[ "ニン", "しのばせる", "しのぶ", "ジン", "むごい" ] },
	{"question":"妊", "answers":[ "ニン", "ジン", "はらむ", "みごもる" ] },
	{"question":"把", "answers":[ "ハ", "とる", "にぎる" ] },
	{"question":"伯", "answers":[ "ハク", "ハ", "おさ", "かしら", "はたがしら" ] },
	{"question":"扶", "answers":[ "フ", "たすける" ] },
	{"question":"戻", "answers":[ "もどす", "もどる", "レイ", "いたる", "もとる" ] },
	{"question":"串", "answers":[ "くし", "カン", "セン", "つらぬく", "なれる" ] },
	{"question":"沙", "answers":[ "サ", "シャ", "すな", "みぎわ", "よなげる" ] },
	{"question":"芯", "answers":[ "シン", "とうしんぐさ" ] },
	{"question":"汰", "answers":[ "タ", "タイ", "おごる", "にごる", "よなげる" ] },
	{"question":"那", "answers":[ "ナ", "ダ", "いかんぞ", "なに", "なんぞ" ] },
	{"question":"阪", "answers":[ "ハン", "さか" ] },
	{"question":"肘", "answers":[ "ひじ", "チュウ" ] },
	{"question":"冶", "answers":[ "ヤ", "いる", "とける", "なまめかしい" ] },
	{"question":"妖", "answers":[ "ヨウ", "あやしい", "なまめかしい", "わざわい" ] },
	{"question":"沃", "answers":[ "ヨク", "オク", "こえる", "そそぐ" ] },
	{"question":"呂", "answers":[ "ロ", "リョ" ] },
	{"question":"弄", "answers":[ "ロウ", "もてあそぶ", "あなどる", "いじくる", "いじる", "いらう", "たわむれる", "まさぐる" ] },
	{"question":"雨", "answers":[ "ウ", "あま", "あめ" ] },
	{"question":"学", "answers":[ "ガク", "まなぶ" ] },
	{"question":"空", "answers":[ "クウ", "あく", "あける", "から", "そら", "あな", "うつける", "うつろ", "うろ", "すく", "むなしい" ] },
	{"question":"金", "answers":[ "キン", "コン", "かな", "かね", "こがね" ] },
	{"question":"青", "answers":[ "セイ", "あお", "あおい", "ショウ" ] },
	{"question":"林", "answers":[ "リン", "はやし", "おおい" ] },
	{"question":"画", "answers":[ "ガ", "カク", "え", "えがく", "かぎる", "かく", "はかる" ] },
	{"question":"岩", "answers":[ "ガン", "いわ" ] },
	{"question":"京", "answers":[ "キョウ", "ケイ", "キン", "みやこ" ] },
	{"question":"国", "answers":[ "コク", "くに" ] },
	{"question":"姉", "answers":[ "あね", "シ" ] },
	{"question":"知", "answers":[ "チ", "しる", "しらせる" ] },
	{"question":"長", "answers":[ "チョウ", "ながい", "ジョウ", "おさ", "たける" ] },
	{"question":"直", "answers":[ "ジキ", "チョク", "ただちに", "なおす", "なおる", "チ", "あたい", "じか", "すぐ", "ひた" ] },
	{"question":"店", "answers":[ "テン", "みせ", "たな" ] },
	{"question":"東", "answers":[ "トウ", "ひがし", "あずま" ] },
	{"question":"歩", "answers":[ "ホ", "あゆむ", "あるく", "ブ", "フ" ] },
	{"question":"妹", "answers":[ "いもうと", "マイ", "バイ", "いも" ] },
	{"question":"明", "answers":[ "ミョウ", "メイ", "あかす", "あからむ", "あかり", "あかるい", "あかるむ", "あきらか", "あく", "あくる", "あける", "ミン" ] },
	{"question":"門", "answers":[ "モン", "かど", "ボン", "いえ", "と", "みうち" ] },
	{"question":"夜", "answers":[ "ヤ", "よ", "よる" ] },
	{"question":"委", "answers":[ "イ", "ゆだねる", "おく", "くわしい", "すてる", "まかせる" ] },
	{"question":"育", "answers":[ "イク", "そだつ", "そだてる", "はぐくむ" ] },
	{"question":"泳", "answers":[ "エイ", "およぐ" ] },
	{"question":"岸", "answers":[ "ガン", "きし", "かどだつ" ] },
	{"question":"苦", "answers":[ "ク", "くるしい", "くるしむ", "くるしめる", "にがい", "にがる", "にがな", "はなはだ" ] },
	{"question":"具", "answers":[ "グ", "つぶさに", "つま", "そなえる", "そなわる" ] },
	{"question":"幸", "answers":[ "コウ", "さいわい", "しあわせ", "さち", "みゆき" ] },
	{"question":"始", "answers":[ "シ", "はじまる", "はじめる" ] },
	{"question":"使", "answers":[ "シ", "つかう", "つかわす" ] },
	{"question":"事", "answers":[ "ジ", "こと", "ズ", "つかえる" ] },
	{"question":"実", "answers":[ "ジツ", "み", "みのる", "さね", "まこと", "まめ", "みちる" ] },
	{"question":"者", "answers":[ "シャ", "もの" ] },
	{"question":"昔", "answers":[ "むかし", "シャク", "セキ" ] },
	{"question":"取", "answers":[ "シュ", "とる" ] },
	{"question":"受", "answers":[ "ジュ", "うかる", "うける", "ズ" ] },
	{"question":"所", "answers":[ "ショ", "ところ", "ソ" ] },
	{"question":"注", "answers":[ "チュウ", "そそぐ", "さす", "つぐ" ] },
	{"question":"定", "answers":[ "ジョウ", "テイ", "さだまる", "さだめる", "さだか", "きまる" ] },
	{"question":"波", "answers":[ "ハ", "なみ" ] },
	{"question":"板", "answers":[ "ハン", "バン", "いた" ] },
	{"question":"表", "answers":[ "ヒョウ", "あらわす", "あらわれる", "おもて", "しるし" ] },
	{"question":"服", "answers":[ "フク", "きもの", "きる", "したがう", "のむ" ] },
	{"question":"物", "answers":[ "ブツ", "モツ", "もの" ] },
	{"question":"放", "answers":[ "ホウ", "はなす", "はなつ", "はなれる", "ほうる", "こく", "さく", "ひる", "ほしいまま", "まかす", "ゆるす" ] },
	{"question":"味", "answers":[ "ミ", "あじ", "あじわう", "ビ" ] },
	{"question":"命", "answers":[ "メイ", "いのち", "ミョウ", "おおせ", "みこと" ] },
	{"question":"油", "answers":[ "ユ", "あぶら", "ユウ" ] },
	{"question":"和", "answers":[ "ワ", "なごむ", "なごやか", "やわらぐ", "やわらげる", "オ", "カ", "あえる", "なぐ" ] },
	{"question":"英", "answers":[ "エイ", "はな", "はなぶさ", "ひいでる" ] },
	{"question":"果", "answers":[ "カ", "はたす", "はて", "はてる", "おおせる", "くだもの", "はか" ] },
	{"question":"芽", "answers":[ "ガ", "め", "めぐむ" ] },
	{"question":"官", "answers":[ "カン", "おおやけ", "つかさ" ] },
	{"question":"季", "answers":[ "キ", "すえ" ] },
	{"question":"泣", "answers":[ "なく", "キュウ" ] },
	{"question":"協", "answers":[ "キョウ", "かなう" ] },
	{"question":"径", "answers":[ "ケイ", "こみち", "さしわたし", "ただちに", "みち" ] },
	{"question":"固", "answers":[ "コ", "かたい", "かたまる", "かためる", "もとより" ] },
	{"question":"刷", "answers":[ "サツ", "する", "はく" ] },
	{"question":"参", "answers":[ "サン", "まいる", "シン", "まじわる" ] },
	{"question":"治", "answers":[ "ジ", "チ", "おさまる", "おさめる", "なおす", "なおる" ] },
	{"question":"周", "answers":[ "シュウ", "まわり", "ス", "あまねく", "めぐる" ] },
	{"question":"松", "answers":[ "ショウ", "まつ" ] },
	{"question":"卒", "answers":[ "ソツ", "シュツ", "おえる", "おわる", "しもべ", "ついに", "にわかに" ] },
	{"question":"底", "answers":[ "テイ", "そこ" ] },
	{"question":"的", "answers":[ "テキ", "まと", "あきらか" ] },
	{"question":"典", "answers":[ "テン", "のり", "ふみ" ] },
	{"question":"毒", "answers":[ "ドク", "そこなう", "わるい" ] },
	{"question":"念", "answers":[ "ネン", "おもう" ] },
	{"question":"府", "answers":[ "フ", "くら", "みやこ" ] },
	{"question":"法", "answers":[ "ホウ", "ハッ", "ホッ", "のっとる", "のり", "フラン" ] },
	{"question":"牧", "answers":[ "ボク", "まき", "モク", "かう", "つかさ", "やしなう" ] },
	{"question":"例", "answers":[ "レイ", "たとえる", "たぐい", "たとえば", "ためし" ] },
	{"question":"易", "answers":[ "イ", "エキ", "やさしい", "あなどる", "かえる", "かわる", "やすい" ] },
	{"question":"往", "answers":[ "オウ", "いにしえ", "ゆく" ] },
	{"question":"価", "answers":[ "カ", "あたい" ] },
	{"question":"河", "answers":[ "カ", "かわ" ] },
	{"question":"居", "answers":[ "キョ", "いる", "キ", "コ", "おく", "おる" ] },
	{"question":"券", "answers":[ "ケン", "てがた", "わりふ" ] },
	{"question":"効", "answers":[ "コウ", "きく", "いたす", "かい", "ならう" ] },
	{"question":"妻", "answers":[ "サイ", "つま", "セイ", "めあわす" ] },
	{"question":"枝", "answers":[ "えだ", "シ" ] },
	{"question":"舎", "answers":[ "シャ", "セキ", "いえ", "おく", "やど", "やどる" ] },
	{"question":"述", "answers":[ "ジュツ", "のべる" ] },
	{"question":"承", "answers":[ "ショウ", "うけたまわる", "うける" ] },
	{"question":"招", "answers":[ "ショウ", "まねく" ] },
	{"question":"性", "answers":[ "セイ", "ショウ", "さが", "たち" ] },
	{"question":"制", "answers":[ "セイ", "おさえる" ] },
	{"question":"版", "answers":[ "ハン", "いた", "ふだ" ] },
	{"question":"肥", "answers":[ "ヒ", "こえ", "こえる", "こやし", "こやす", "ふとる" ] },
	{"question":"非", "answers":[ "ヒ", "あらず", "そしる", "わるい" ] },
	{"question":"武", "answers":[ "ブ", "ム", "たけし", "もののふ" ] },
	{"question":"沿", "answers":[ "エン", "そう", "ふち" ] },
	{"question":"延", "answers":[ "エン", "のばす", "のびる", "のべる", "はえ", "ひく" ] },
	{"question":"拡", "answers":[ "カク", "ひろがる", "ひろげる" ] },
	{"question":"供", "answers":[ "キョウ", "そなえる", "とも", "ク" ] },
	{"question":"呼", "answers":[ "コ", "よぶ" ] },
	{"question":"刻", "answers":[ "コク", "きざむ", "とき" ] },
	{"question":"若", "answers":[ "わかい", "ジャク", "ニャク", "もしくは", "ジャ", "ニャ", "ごとし", "しく", "なんじ", "もし" ] },
	{"question":"宗", "answers":[ "シュウ", "ソウ", "むね" ] },
	{"question":"垂", "answers":[ "スイ", "たらす", "たれる", "しだれる", "しで", "なんなんとする" ] },
	{"question":"担", "answers":[ "タン", "かつぐ", "になう", "ケツ" ] },
	{"question":"宙", "answers":[ "チュウ", "そら" ] },
	{"question":"忠", "answers":[ "チュウ", "まごころ" ] },
	{"question":"届", "answers":[ "とどく", "とどける", "カイ" ] },
	{"question":"乳", "answers":[ "ニュウ", "ちち", "ち", "ジュ", "ニュ" ] },
	{"question":"拝", "answers":[ "ハイ", "おがむ" ] },
	{"question":"並", "answers":[ "なみ", "ならびに", "ならぶ", "ならべる", "ヘイ" ] },
	{"question":"宝", "answers":[ "ホウ", "たから" ] },
	{"question":"枚", "answers":[ "マイ", "バイ", "ひら" ] },
	{"question":"依", "answers":[ "イ", "エ", "よる" ] },
	{"question":"押", "answers":[ "おさえる", "おす", "オウ" ] },
	{"question":"奇", "answers":[ "キ", "あやしい", "くし", "めずらしい" ] },
	{"question":"祈", "answers":[ "キ", "いのる" ] },
	{"question":"拠", "answers":[ "キョ", "コ", "よりどころ", "よる" ] },
	{"question":"況", "answers":[ "キョウ", "ありさま", "いわんや" ] },
	{"question":"屈", "answers":[ "クツ", "かがむ", "くぐまる", "こごまる" ] },
	{"question":"肩", "answers":[ "かた", "ケン" ] },
	{"question":"刺", "answers":[ "シ", "ささる", "さす", "セキ", "そしる", "とげ", "なふだ" ] },
	{"question":"沼", "answers":[ "ぬま", "ショウ" ] },
	{"question":"征", "answers":[ "セイ", "うつ", "とる", "ゆく" ] },
	{"question":"姓", "answers":[ "ショウ", "セイ", "かばね" ] },
	{"question":"拓", "answers":[ "タク", "セキ", "ひらく" ] },
	{"question":"抵", "answers":[ "テイ", "シ", "あたる", "うつ", "ふれる" ] },
	{"question":"到", "answers":[ "トウ", "いたる" ] },
	{"question":"突", "answers":[ "トツ", "つく" ] },
	{"question":"杯", "answers":[ "ハイ", "さかずき" ] },
	{"question":"泊", "answers":[ "ハク", "とまる", "とめる" ] },
	{"question":"拍", "answers":[ "ハク", "ヒョウ", "うつ" ] },
	{"question":"迫", "answers":[ "ハク", "せまる", "せる" ] },
	{"question":"彼", "answers":[ "ヒ", "かの", "かれ" ] },
	{"question":"怖", "answers":[ "フ", "こわい", "おじける", "おそれる" ] },
	{"question":"抱", "answers":[ "ホウ", "いだく", "かかえる", "だく" ] },
	{"question":"肪", "answers":[ "ボウ", "ホウ", "あぶら" ] },
	{"question":"茂", "answers":[ "モ", "しげる", "ボウ", "すぐれる" ] },
	{"question":"炎", "answers":[ "エン", "ほのお", "ほむら", "もえる" ] },
	{"question":"欧", "answers":[ "オウ", "はく" ] },
	{"question":"殴", "answers":[ "なぐる", "オウ", "うつ", "たたく" ] },
	{"question":"佳", "answers":[ "カ", "よい" ] },
	{"question":"怪", "answers":[ "カイ", "あやしい", "あやしむ", "ケ" ] },
	{"question":"岳", "answers":[ "ガク", "たけ" ] },
	{"question":"拘", "answers":[ "コウ", "かかわる", "こだわる", "とどめる", "とらえる" ] },
	{"question":"祉", "answers":[ "シ", "さいわい" ] },
	{"question":"侍", "answers":[ "ジ", "さむらい", "シ", "さぶらう", "はべる" ] },
	{"question":"邪", "answers":[ "ジャ", "シャ", "ヤ", "よこしま" ] },
	{"question":"昇", "answers":[ "ショウ", "のぼる" ] },
	{"question":"炊", "answers":[ "スイ", "たく", "かしぐ" ] },
	{"question":"阻", "answers":[ "ソ", "はばむ", "けわしい", "へだたる" ] },
	{"question":"卓", "answers":[ "タク", "シツ", "すぐれる", "つくえ" ] },
	{"question":"抽", "answers":[ "チュウ", "ぬく", "ひく" ] },
	{"question":"泌", "answers":[ "ヒツ", "ヒ", "にじむ" ] },
	{"question":"苗", "answers":[ "なえ", "なわ", "ビョウ", "ミョウ", "かり" ] },
	{"question":"奉", "answers":[ "ブ", "ホウ", "たてまつる", "うけたまわる", "まつる" ] },
	{"question":"房", "answers":[ "ボウ", "ふさ", "ホウ", "いえ", "へや" ] },
	{"question":"免", "answers":[ "メン", "まぬかれる", "ブン", "ベン", "うむ", "やめる", "ゆるす" ] },
	{"question":"炉", "answers":[ "ロ", "いろり", "ひばち" ] },
	{"question":"拐", "answers":[ "カイ", "かたる", "かどわかす" ] },
	{"question":"劾", "answers":[ "ガイ", "カイ", "あばく", "しらべる" ] },
	{"question":"宜", "answers":[ "ギ", "むべ", "よい", "よろしい", "よろしく" ] },
	{"question":"拒", "answers":[ "キョ", "こばむ", "ふせぐ" ] },
	{"question":"享", "answers":[ "キョウ", "あたる", "うける", "すすめる" ] },
	{"question":"茎", "answers":[ "ケイ", "くき", "なかご" ] },
	{"question":"弦", "answers":[ "ゲン", "つる" ] },
	{"question":"肯", "answers":[ "コウ", "あえて", "うなずく", "うべなう", "がえんじる" ] },
	{"question":"昆", "answers":[ "コン", "あに" ] },
	{"question":"肢", "answers":[ "シ", "てあし" ] },
	{"question":"叔", "answers":[ "シュク", "わかい" ] },
	{"question":"尚", "answers":[ "ショウ", "くわえる", "たっとぶ", "とうとぶ", "なお" ] },
	{"question":"枢", "answers":[ "スウ", "かなめ", "とぼそ" ] },
	{"question":"斉", "answers":[ "セイ", "サイ", "シ", "ととのえる", "ひとしい", "ものいみ" ] },
	{"question":"析", "answers":[ "セキ", "さく", "わかれる", "わける" ] },
	{"question":"拙", "answers":[ "セツ", "つたない", "まずい" ] },
	{"question":"坪", "answers":[ "つぼ", "ヘイ" ] },
	{"question":"邸", "answers":[ "テイ", "やしき" ] },
	{"question":"泥", "answers":[ "どろ", "デイ", "なずむ" ] },
	{"question":"迭", "answers":[ "テツ", "かわる", "たがいに" ] },
	{"question":"披", "answers":[ "ヒ", "ひらく" ] },
	{"question":"附", "answers":[ "フ", "ブ", "つく", "つける" ] },
	{"question":"侮", "answers":[ "ブ", "あなどる" ] },
	{"question":"沸", "answers":[ "フツ", "わかす", "わく", "ヒ", "たてる", "にえ" ] },
	{"question":"併", "answers":[ "ヘイ", "あわせる", "しかし", "ならぶ" ] },
	{"question":"泡", "answers":[ "ホウ", "あわ", "あぶく" ] },
	{"question":"奔", "answers":[ "ホン", "はしる" ] },
	{"question":"抹", "answers":[ "マツ", "バツ", "けす", "こな", "する" ] },
	{"question":"岬", "answers":[ "みさき", "コウ" ] },
	{"question":"盲", "answers":[ "モウ", "ボウ", "くらい", "めくら" ] },
	{"question":"枠", "answers":[ "わく" ] },
	{"question":"宛", "answers":[ "あてる", "エン", "あたかも", "あて", "さながら", "ずつ" ] },
	{"question":"旺", "answers":[ "オウ", "さかん" ] },
	{"question":"岡", "answers":[ "おか", "コウ" ] },
	{"question":"苛", "answers":[ "カ", "いじめる", "いらだつ", "からい", "きびしい", "さいなむ", "むごい", "わずらわしい" ] },
	{"question":"玩", "answers":[ "ガン", "あじわう", "もてあそぶ" ] },
	{"question":"股", "answers":[ "コ", "また", "もも" ] },
	{"question":"虎", "answers":[ "コ", "とら" ] },
	{"question":"采", "answers":[ "サイ", "いろどり", "うね", "すがた", "とる" ] },
	{"question":"刹", "answers":[ "セツ", "サツ", "てら" ] },
	{"question":"呪", "answers":[ "ジュ", "のろう", "シュ", "シュウ", "まじない", "まじなう" ] },
	{"question":"狙", "answers":[ "ソ", "ねらう", "さる" ] },
	{"question":"妬", "answers":[ "ト", "ねたむ", "そねむ", "やく" ] },
	{"question":"奈", "answers":[ "ナ", "ダイ", "ナイ", "いかん", "いかんぞ", "なんぞ" ] },
	{"question":"阜", "answers":[ "フ", "おか", "ゆたか" ] },
	{"question":"枕", "answers":[ "まくら", "シン", "チン" ] },
	{"question":"弥", "answers":[ "や", "ビ", "ミ", "あまねし", "いや", "いよいよ", "つくろう", "ひさしい", "わたる" ] },
	{"question":"拉", "answers":[ "ラ", "ラツ", "ロウ", "くじく", "ひく", "ひしぐ", "ひしゃげる" ] },
	{"question":"音", "answers":[ "オン", "おと", "ね", "イン", "たより" ] },
	{"question":"草", "answers":[ "ソウ", "くさ" ] },
	{"question":"科", "answers":[ "カ", "しぐさ", "しな", "とが" ] },
	{"question":"海", "answers":[ "カイ", "うみ" ] },
	{"question":"活", "answers":[ "カツ", "いかす", "いきる", "いける" ] },
	{"question":"計", "answers":[ "ケイ", "はからう", "はかる", "かぞえる" ] },
	{"question":"後", "answers":[ "ゴ", "コウ", "あと", "うしろ", "のち", "おくれる", "しり" ] },
	{"question":"室", "answers":[ "シツ", "むろ", "いえ", "つま", "へや" ] },
	{"question":"首", "answers":[ "シュ", "くび", "かしら", "こうべ", "はじめ", "もうす" ] },
	{"question":"秋", "answers":[ "シュウ", "あき", "とき" ] },
	{"question":"春", "answers":[ "シュン", "はる" ] },
	{"question":"食", "answers":[ "ショク", "くう", "たべる", "ジキ", "くらう", "イ", "シ", "はむ" ] },
	{"question":"星", "answers":[ "セイ", "ほし", "ショウ" ] },
	{"question":"前", "answers":[ "ゼン", "まえ", "セン", "さき" ] },
	{"question":"茶", "answers":[ "チャ", "サ" ] },
	{"question":"昼", "answers":[ "チュウ", "ひる" ] },
	{"question":"点", "answers":[ "テン", "たてる", "つける", "とぼす", "とぼる", "ともる" ] },
	{"question":"南", "answers":[ "ナン", "みなみ", "ナ", "ダン" ] },
	{"question":"風", "answers":[ "フウ", "かざ", "かぜ", "フ", "すがた", "ならわし", "ふり" ] },
	{"question":"屋", "answers":[ "オク", "や", "いえ", "やね" ] },
	{"question":"界", "answers":[ "カイ", "さかい" ] },
	{"question":"客", "answers":[ "キャク", "カク", "まろうど" ] },
	{"question":"急", "answers":[ "キュウ", "いそぐ", "せく" ] },
	{"question":"級", "answers":[ "キュウ", "くび", "しな" ] },
	{"question":"係", "answers":[ "ケイ", "かかり", "かかる", "かかわる", "つなぐ" ] },
	{"question":"県", "answers":[ "ケン", "あがた" ] },
	{"question":"研", "answers":[ "ケン", "とぐ", "ゲン", "みがく" ] },
	{"question":"指", "answers":[ "シ", "さす", "ゆび" ] },
	{"question":"持", "answers":[ "ジ", "もつ", "チ" ] },
	{"question":"拾", "answers":[ "ひろう", "シュウ", "ジュウ", "とお" ] },
	{"question":"重", "answers":[ "ジュウ", "チョウ", "おもい", "かさなる", "かさねる", "え", "おもんじる" ] },
	{"question":"昭", "answers":[ "ショウ", "あきらか" ] },
	{"question":"乗", "answers":[ "ジョウ", "のせる", "のる", "ショウ" ] },
	{"question":"神", "answers":[ "シン", "ジン", "かみ", "かん", "こう", "たましい" ] },
	{"question":"相", "answers":[ "ソウ", "あい", "ショウ", "ありさま", "さが", "たすける" ] },
	{"question":"送", "answers":[ "ソウ", "おくる" ] },
	{"question":"待", "answers":[ "タイ", "まつ" ] },
	{"question":"炭", "answers":[ "タン", "すみ" ] },
	{"question":"柱", "answers":[ "チュウ", "はしら" ] },
	{"question":"追", "answers":[ "ツイ", "おう" ] },
	{"question":"度", "answers":[ "ド", "タク", "たび", "ト", "のり", "はかる", "めもり", "わたる" ] },
	{"question":"畑", "answers":[ "はた", "はたけ" ] },
	{"question":"発", "answers":[ "ハツ", "ホツ", "あばく", "たつ", "はなつ", "ひらく" ] },
	{"question":"美", "answers":[ "ビ", "うつくしい", "ミ", "ほめる", "よい" ] },
	{"question":"秒", "answers":[ "ビョウ", "のぎ" ] },
	{"question":"品", "answers":[ "ヒン", "しな", "ホン" ] },
	{"question":"負", "answers":[ "フ", "おう", "まかす", "まける", "ブ", "フウ", "そむく", "たのむ" ] },
	{"question":"面", "answers":[ "メン", "おも", "おもて", "つら", "ベン", "そむく", "も" ] },
	{"question":"洋", "answers":[ "ヨウ", "うみ", "なだ", "ひろい" ] },
	{"question":"胃", "answers":[ "イ" ] },
	{"question":"栄", "answers":[ "エイ", "さかえる", "はえ", "はえる", "はやす" ] },
	{"question":"紀", "answers":[ "キ", "おさめる", "しるす", "のり" ] },
	{"question":"軍", "answers":[ "グン", "クン", "いくさ", "つわもの" ] },
	{"question":"型", "answers":[ "ケイ", "かた" ] },
	{"question":"建", "answers":[ "ケン", "たつ", "たてる", "コン", "くつがえす" ] },
	{"question":"律", "answers":[ "リツ", "リチ", "のっとる", "のり" ] },
	{"question":"昨", "answers":[ "サク", "きのう" ] },
	{"question":"祝", "answers":[ "シュク", "いわう", "シュウ", "たつ", "のる", "のろう" ] },
	{"question":"省", "answers":[ "ショウ", "セイ", "はぶく", "かえりみる" ] },
	{"question":"信", "answers":[ "シン", "たより", "まかせる", "まこと" ] },
	{"question":"浅", "answers":[ "あさい", "セン" ] },
	{"question":"単", "answers":[ "タン", "ゼン", "ひとえ", "ひとつ" ] },
	{"question":"飛", "answers":[ "ヒ", "とばす", "とぶ" ] },
	{"question":"変", "answers":[ "ヘン", "かえる", "かわる" ] },
	{"question":"便", "answers":[ "ビン", "ベン", "たより", "ヘン", "いばり", "すなわち", "へつらう", "よすが" ] },
	{"question":"約", "answers":[ "ヤク", "ちかう", "つづまやか", "つづめる", "つましい" ] },
	{"question":"勇", "answers":[ "ユウ", "いさむ", "ヨウ", "いさましい", "つよい" ] },
	{"question":"要", "answers":[ "ヨウ", "かなめ", "いる", "もとめる" ] },
	{"question":"逆", "answers":[ "ギャク", "さか", "さからう", "ゲキ", "あらかじめ", "むかえる" ] },
	{"question":"限", "answers":[ "ゲン", "かぎる", "かぎり", "きり" ] },
	{"question":"故", "answers":[ "コ", "ゆえ", "ことさらに", "ふるい", "もと" ] },
	{"question":"厚", "answers":[ "あつい", "コウ" ] },
	{"question":"査", "answers":[ "サ", "しらべる" ] },
	{"question":"政", "answers":[ "セイ", "ショウ", "まつりごと" ] },
	{"question":"祖", "answers":[ "ソ", "おや", "じじ", "はじめ" ] },
	{"question":"則", "answers":[ "ソク", "すなわち", "のっとる", "のり" ] },
	{"question":"退", "answers":[ "タイ", "しりぞく", "しりぞける", "しさる", "すさる", "のく", "のける", "ひく" ] },
	{"question":"独", "answers":[ "ドク", "ひとり", "トク" ] },
	{"question":"保", "answers":[ "ホ", "たもつ", "ホウ", "もつ", "やすんじる" ] },
	{"question":"迷", "answers":[ "まよう", "メイ", "まどう" ] },
	{"question":"映", "answers":[ "エイ", "うつす", "うつる", "はえる", "はやす" ] },
	{"question":"革", "answers":[ "カク", "かわ", "キョク", "あらたまる", "あらためる" ] },
	{"question":"看", "answers":[ "カン", "みる" ] },
	{"question":"巻", "answers":[ "カン", "まき", "まく", "ケン" ] },
	{"question":"皇", "answers":[ "オウ", "コウ", "きみ", "すめらぎ" ] },
	{"question":"紅", "answers":[ "コウ", "べに", "ク", "くれない", "グ", "あかい", "もみ" ] },
	{"question":"砂", "answers":[ "サ", "すな", "シャ", "いさご" ] },
	{"question":"姿", "answers":[ "シ", "すがた" ] },
	{"question":"城", "answers":[ "ジョウ", "しろ", "セイ", "き" ] },
	{"question":"専", "answers":[ "セン", "もっぱら", "ほしいまま" ] },
	{"question":"宣", "answers":[ "セン", "のたまう", "のべる" ] },
	{"question":"染", "answers":[ "そまる", "そめる", "セン", "しみ", "しみる", "ゼン" ] },
	{"question":"泉", "answers":[ "セン", "いずみ" ] },
	{"question":"洗", "answers":[ "セン", "あらう", "セイ" ] },
	{"question":"奏", "answers":[ "ソウ", "かなでる", "すすめる" ] },
	{"question":"段", "answers":[ "ダン", "タン", "きざはし" ] },
	{"question":"派", "answers":[ "ハ", "ハイ", "つかわす", "わかれる" ] },
	{"question":"肺", "answers":[ "ハイ" ] },
	{"question":"背", "answers":[ "ハイ", "せ", "せい", "そむく", "そむける", "うしろ" ] },
	{"question":"威", "answers":[ "イ", "おどす" ] },
	{"question":"為", "answers":[ "イ", "する", "ため", "つくる", "なす", "なる" ] },
	{"question":"皆", "answers":[ "カイ", "みな" ] },
	{"question":"狭", "answers":[ "せばまる", "せばめる", "せまい", "キョウ", "コウ", "さ" ] },
	{"question":"枯", "answers":[ "コ", "からす", "かれる", "からびる" ] },
	{"question":"荒", "answers":[ "コウ", "あらい", "あらす", "あれる", "すさぶ", "すさむ" ] },
	{"question":"香", "answers":[ "コウ", "か", "かおり", "かおる", "キョウ", "かぐわしい", "かんばしい" ] },
	{"question":"恒", "answers":[ "コウ", "つね", "つねに" ] },
	{"question":"咲", "answers":[ "さく", "ショウ", "わらう" ] },
	{"question":"狩", "answers":[ "シュ", "かり", "かる" ] },
	{"question":"柔", "answers":[ "ジュウ", "ニュウ", "やわらか", "やわらかい", "やさしい", "やわらげる" ] },
	{"question":"盾", "answers":[ "ジュン", "たて" ] },
	{"question":"侵", "answers":[ "シン", "おかす", "みにくい" ] },
	{"question":"是", "answers":[ "ゼ", "シ", "この", "これ", "ただしい" ] },
	{"question":"俗", "answers":[ "ゾク", "いやしい", "ならわし" ] },
	{"question":"耐", "answers":[ "タイ", "たえる", "ダイ", "ドウ", "ナイ", "ノウ" ] },
	{"question":"珍", "answers":[ "チン", "めずらしい" ] },
	{"question":"怒", "answers":[ "ド", "いかる", "おこる", "ヌ" ] },
	{"question":"逃", "answers":[ "トウ", "にがす", "にげる", "のがす", "のがれる" ] },
	{"question":"峠", "answers":[ "とうげ" ] },
	{"question":"柄", "answers":[ "え", "がら", "ヘイ", "いきおい", "つか" ] },
	{"question":"冒", "answers":[ "ボウ", "おかす", "ボク", "モウ", "おおう", "ねたむ", "むさぼる" ] },
	{"question":"盆", "answers":[ "ボン", "ホン", "はち" ] },
	{"question":"郎", "answers":[ "ロウ", "おとこ" ] },
	{"question":"哀", "answers":[ "アイ", "あわれ", "あわれむ", "かなしい", "かなしむ" ] },
	{"question":"卸", "answers":[ "おろし", "おろす", "シャ" ] },
	{"question":"架", "answers":[ "カ", "かかる", "かける", "たな" ] },
	{"question":"悔", "answers":[ "カイ", "くいる", "くやしい", "くやむ", "ケ" ] },
	{"question":"冠", "answers":[ "カン", "かんむり", "かむる" ] },
	{"question":"軌", "answers":[ "キ", "わだち" ] },
	{"question":"虐", "answers":[ "ギャク", "しいたげる", "むごい" ] },
	{"question":"峡", "answers":[ "キョウ", "はざま" ] },
	{"question":"契", "answers":[ "ケイ", "ちぎる", "キツ", "ケツ", "セツ", "きざむ", "ちぎり", "わりふ" ] },
	{"question":"弧", "answers":[ "コ", "きゆみ" ] },
	{"question":"孤", "answers":[ "コ", "そむく", "ひとり", "みなしご" ] },
	{"question":"郊", "answers":[ "コウ" ] },
	{"question":"恨", "answers":[ "コン", "うらむ", "うらめしい" ] },
	{"question":"削", "answers":[ "サク", "けずる", "ショウ", "そぐ", "はつる" ] },
	{"question":"施", "answers":[ "シ", "ほどこす", "セ", "しく" ] },
	{"question":"牲", "answers":[ "セイ", "いけにえ" ] },
	{"question":"促", "answers":[ "ソク", "うながす", "せまる" ] },
	{"question":"胎", "answers":[ "タイ", "はらむ" ] },
	{"question":"怠", "answers":[ "タイ", "おこたる", "なまける", "だるい" ] },
	{"question":"胆", "answers":[ "タン", "トウ", "きも" ] },
	{"question":"訂", "answers":[ "テイ", "さだめる", "ただす" ] },
	{"question":"帝", "answers":[ "テイ", "タイ", "みかど" ] },
	{"question":"卑", "answers":[ "ヒ", "いやしい", "いやしむ", "いやしめる", "ひくい" ] },
	{"question":"赴", "answers":[ "フ", "おもむく", "つげる" ] },
	{"question":"封", "answers":[ "フウ", "ホウ", "さかい", "とじる", "ポンド" ] },
	{"question":"胞", "answers":[ "ホウ", "はら" ] },
	{"question":"某", "answers":[ "ボウ", "バイ", "それがし", "なにがし" ] },
	{"question":"幽", "answers":[ "ユウ", "かすか", "くらい" ] },
	{"question":"厘", "answers":[ "リン", "テン", "デン", "リ" ] },
	{"question":"姻", "answers":[ "イン", "とつぐ" ] },
	{"question":"疫", "answers":[ "エキ", "ヤク" ] },
	{"question":"垣", "answers":[ "かき", "エン" ] },
	{"question":"括", "answers":[ "カツ", "くくる", "くびる", "くびれる" ] },
	{"question":"糾", "answers":[ "キュウ", "あざなう", "ただす" ] },
	{"question":"挟", "answers":[ "はさまる", "はさむ", "キョウ", "さしはさむ" ] },
	{"question":"洪", "answers":[ "コウ", "おおみず" ] },
	{"question":"侯", "answers":[ "コウ", "きみ", "まと" ] },
	{"question":"拷", "answers":[ "ゴウ", "コウ", "うつ" ] },
	{"question":"砕", "answers":[ "サイ", "くだく", "くだける" ] },
	{"question":"臭", "answers":[ "シュウ", "くさい", "におう", "キュウ" ] },
	{"question":"俊", "answers":[ "シュン", "すぐれる" ] },
	{"question":"叙", "answers":[ "ジョ", "のべる" ] },
	{"question":"浄", "answers":[ "ジョウ", "きよい" ] },
	{"question":"津", "answers":[ "つ", "シン", "しる" ] },
	{"question":"甚", "answers":[ "はなはだ", "はなはだしい", "ジン", "いたく" ] },
	{"question":"帥", "answers":[ "スイ", "ソツ", "ひきいる" ] },
	{"question":"窃", "answers":[ "セツ", "ぬすむ", "ひそかに" ] },
	{"question":"荘", "answers":[ "ソウ", "ショウ", "おごそか", "しもやしき" ] },
	{"question":"衷", "answers":[ "チュウ", "うち", "こころ", "まこと" ] },
	{"question":"挑", "answers":[ "チョウ", "いどむ", "トウ" ] },
	{"question":"勅", "answers":[ "チョク", "いましめる", "みことのり" ] },
	{"question":"亭", "answers":[ "テイ", "チン", "あずまや", "とどまる" ] },
	{"question":"貞", "answers":[ "テイ", "ジョウ", "ただしい" ] },
	{"question":"洞", "answers":[ "ドウ", "ほら", "トウ", "うつろ", "うろ", "つらぬく", "ふかい" ] },
	{"question":"柳", "answers":[ "リュウ", "やなぎ" ] },
	{"question":"畏", "answers":[ "イ", "おそれる", "かしこい", "かしこまる" ] },
	{"question":"茨", "answers":[ "いばら", "シ", "くさぶき" ] },
	{"question":"咽", "answers":[ "イン", "エツ", "エン", "のど", "のむ", "むせぶ", "むせる" ] },
	{"question":"怨", "answers":[ "オン", "エン", "うらみ", "うらむ" ] },
	{"question":"柿", "answers":[ "かき", "シ" ] },
	{"question":"柵", "answers":[ "サク", "しがらみ", "とりで", "やらい" ] },
	{"question":"拶", "answers":[ "サツ", "せまる" ] },
	{"question":"拭", "answers":[ "ぬぐう", "ふく", "ショク", "シキ" ] },
	{"question":"栃", "answers":[ "とち" ] },
	{"question":"虹", "answers":[ "にじ", "コウ" ] },
	{"question":"眉", "answers":[ "ミ", "まゆ", "ビ", "としより", "ふち" ] },
	{"question":"訃", "answers":[ "フ", "しらせ", "つげる" ] },
	{"question":"勃", "answers":[ "ボツ", "ホツ", "おこる", "にわかに" ] },
	{"question":"昧", "answers":[ "マイ", "バイ", "くらい" ] },
	{"question":"侶", "answers":[ "リョ", "ロ", "とも" ] },
	{"question":"思", "answers":[ "シ", "おもう", "おぼしい" ] },
	{"question":"校", "answers":[ "コウ", "キョウ", "あぜ", "かせ", "かんがえる", "くらべる" ] },
	{"question":"家", "answers":[ "カ", "ケ", "いえ", "や", "うち" ] },
	{"question":"夏", "answers":[ "カ", "なつ", "ゲ" ] },
	{"question":"記", "answers":[ "キ", "しるす" ] },
	{"question":"帰", "answers":[ "キ", "かえす", "かえる", "おくる", "とつぐ" ] },
	{"question":"原", "answers":[ "ゲン", "はら", "たずねる", "もと", "ゆるす" ] },
	{"question":"高", "answers":[ "コウ", "たか", "たかい", "たかまる", "たかめる" ] },
	{"question":"紙", "answers":[ "シ", "かみ" ] },
	{"question":"時", "answers":[ "ジ", "とき" ] },
	{"question":"弱", "answers":[ "ジャク", "よわい", "よわまる", "よわめる", "よわる", "ニャク" ] },
	{"question":"書", "answers":[ "ショ", "かく", "ふみ" ] },
	{"question":"通", "answers":[ "ツウ", "かよう", "とおす", "とおる", "ツ" ] },
	{"question":"馬", "answers":[ "バ", "うま", "ま", "マ", "メ" ] },
	{"question":"院", "answers":[ "イン", "かき", "かこい" ] },
	{"question":"員", "answers":[ "イン", "エン", "ウン", "かず" ] },
	{"question":"荷", "answers":[ "に", "カ", "になう", "はす" ] },
	{"question":"起", "answers":[ "キ", "おきる", "おこす", "おこる", "たつ" ] },
	{"question":"宮", "answers":[ "キュウ", "みや", "グウ", "ク", "いえ" ] },
	{"question":"庫", "answers":[ "コ", "ク", "くら" ] },
	{"question":"根", "answers":[ "コン", "ね" ] },
	{"question":"酒", "answers":[ "シュ", "さか", "さけ" ] },
	{"question":"消", "answers":[ "ショウ", "きえる", "けす" ] },
	{"question":"真", "answers":[ "シン", "ま", "まこと" ] },
	{"question":"息", "answers":[ "ソク", "いき", "いこう", "やすむ", "やむ" ] },
	{"question":"速", "answers":[ "ソク", "はやい", "はやまる", "はやめる", "すみやか" ] },
	{"question":"庭", "answers":[ "テイ", "にわ" ] },
	{"question":"島", "answers":[ "トウ", "しま" ] },
	{"question":"配", "answers":[ "ハイ", "くばる", "つれあい", "ながす", "ならぶ" ] },
	{"question":"倍", "answers":[ "バイ", "ハイ", "そむく", "ます" ] },
	{"question":"病", "answers":[ "ビョウ", "やまい", "やむ", "ヘイ" ] },
	{"question":"勉", "answers":[ "ベン", "つとめる" ] },
	{"question":"旅", "answers":[ "リョ", "たび", "ロ", "いくさ" ] },
	{"question":"流", "answers":[ "リュウ", "ながす", "ながれる", "ル" ] },
	{"question":"案", "answers":[ "アン", "かんがえる", "つくえ" ] },
	{"question":"害", "answers":[ "ガイ", "カイ", "カツ", "そこなう", "わざわい" ] },
	{"question":"挙", "answers":[ "キョ", "あがる", "あげる", "こぞって", "こぞる" ] },
	{"question":"訓", "answers":[ "クン", "キン", "おしえる", "よむ" ] },
	{"question":"郡", "answers":[ "グン", "クン", "こおり" ] },
	{"question":"候", "answers":[ "コウ", "そうろう", "うかがう", "さぶらう", "まつ" ] },
	{"question":"航", "answers":[ "コウ", "わたる" ] },
	{"question":"差", "answers":[ "サ", "さす", "サイ", "シ", "たがう", "つかわす" ] },
	{"question":"殺", "answers":[ "サツ", "ころす", "サイ", "セツ", "あやめる", "けずる", "そぐ", "そげる" ] },
	{"question":"残", "answers":[ "ザン", "のこす", "のこる", "そこなう" ] },
	{"question":"借", "answers":[ "シャク", "かりる", "シャ" ] },
	{"question":"笑", "answers":[ "わらう", "ショウ", "えむ" ] },
	{"question":"席", "answers":[ "セキ", "むしろ" ] },
	{"question":"倉", "answers":[ "ソウ", "くら", "にわか" ] },
	{"question":"孫", "answers":[ "ソン", "まご" ] },
	{"question":"帯", "answers":[ "タイ", "おび", "おびる" ] },
	{"question":"徒", "answers":[ "ト", "ズ", "あだ", "いたずらに", "かち", "ただ", "ともがら", "むだ" ] },
	{"question":"特", "answers":[ "トク", "ドク", "おうし", "とりわけ", "ひとつ", "ひとり" ] },
	{"question":"梅", "answers":[ "バイ", "うめ" ] },
	{"question":"粉", "answers":[ "フン", "こ", "こな", "デシメトル" ] },
	{"question":"脈", "answers":[ "ミャク", "バク", "すじ" ] },
	{"question":"浴", "answers":[ "ヨク", "あびせる", "あびる", "ゆあみ" ] },
	{"question":"料", "answers":[ "リョウ", "はかる" ] },
	{"question":"連", "answers":[ "レン", "つらなる", "つらねる", "つれる", "しきりに" ] },
	{"question":"益", "answers":[ "エキ", "ヤク", "ます", "ますます" ] },
	{"question":"桜", "answers":[ "さくら", "オウ" ] },
	{"question":"恩", "answers":[ "オン", "めぐみ" ] },
	{"question":"格", "answers":[ "カク", "コウ", "キャク", "ゴウ", "いたる", "うつ", "ただす" ] },
	{"question":"個", "answers":[ "コ", "カ" ] },
	{"question":"耕", "answers":[ "コウ", "たがやす" ] },
	{"question":"財", "answers":[ "ザイ", "サイ", "たから" ] },
	{"question":"師", "answers":[ "シ", "いくさ", "みやこ" ] },
	{"question":"修", "answers":[ "シュウ", "おさまる", "おさめる", "シュ", "かざる", "ながい" ] },
	{"question":"素", "answers":[ "ソ", "ス", "しろい", "もと", "もとより" ] },
	{"question":"造", "answers":[ "ゾウ", "つくる", "いたる", "なる", "はじめる", "みやつこ" ] },
	{"question":"能", "answers":[ "ノウ", "ダイ", "ドウ", "あたう", "はたらき", "よく", "よくする" ] },
	{"question":"破", "answers":[ "ハ", "やぶる", "やぶれる", "われる" ] },
	{"question":"俵", "answers":[ "ヒョウ", "たわら" ] },
	{"question":"容", "answers":[ "ヨウ", "いれる", "かたち", "ゆるす" ] },
	{"question":"留", "answers":[ "リュウ", "ル", "とまる", "とめる", "とどまる", "とどめる" ] },
	{"question":"株", "answers":[ "かぶ", "シュ" ] },
	{"question":"胸", "answers":[ "キョウ", "むね", "むな", "こころ" ] },
	{"question":"降", "answers":[ "コウ", "おりる", "おろす", "ふる", "ゴウ", "くだす", "くだる" ] },
	{"question":"骨", "answers":[ "コツ", "ほね" ] },
	{"question":"座", "answers":[ "ザ", "すわる", "います" ] },
	{"question":"蚕", "answers":[ "サン", "かいこ", "テン", "こ" ] },
	{"question":"射", "answers":[ "シャ", "いる", "エキ", "セキ", "ヤ", "あてる", "うつ", "さす" ] },
	{"question":"従", "answers":[ "ジュウ", "したがう", "したがえる", "ジュ", "ショウ" ] },
	{"question":"純", "answers":[ "ジュン", "トン", "きいと" ] },
	{"question":"除", "answers":[ "ジョ", "のぞく", "ジ", "つきる", "のける", "はらう", "よける" ] },
	{"question":"将", "answers":[ "ショウ", "はた", "ひきいる", "まさに" ] },
	{"question":"針", "answers":[ "シン", "はり" ] },
	{"question":"値", "answers":[ "チ", "ね", "あたい", "チョク", "あう" ] },
	{"question":"展", "answers":[ "テン", "つらねる", "のべる", "ひろげる" ] },
	{"question":"党", "answers":[ "トウ", "なかま", "むら" ] },
	{"question":"討", "answers":[ "トウ", "うつ", "たずねる" ] },
	{"question":"納", "answers":[ "ノウ", "おさまる", "おさめる", "トウ", "ナッ", "ナ", "ナン", "いれる" ] },
	{"question":"俳", "answers":[ "ハイ", "たわむれ", "わざおぎ" ] },
	{"question":"班", "answers":[ "ハン", "かえす", "わける" ] },
	{"question":"秘", "answers":[ "ヒ", "ひめる", "かくす", "ひそか" ] },
	{"question":"陛", "answers":[ "ヘイ", "きざはし" ] },
	{"question":"鬼", "answers":[ "キ", "おに" ] },
	{"question":"恐", "answers":[ "キョウ", "おそれる", "おそろしい", "こわい" ] },
	{"question":"恵", "answers":[ "エ", "ケイ", "めぐむ" ] },
	{"question":"兼", "answers":[ "ケン", "かねる", "あわせる" ] },
	{"question":"軒", "answers":[ "ケン", "のき", "くるま", "たかい", "てすり", "とぶ" ] },
	{"question":"剣", "answers":[ "ケン", "つるぎ" ] },
	{"question":"剤", "answers":[ "ザイ", "スイ", "セイ", "まぜる" ] },
	{"question":"脂", "answers":[ "シ", "あぶら", "べに", "やに" ] },
	{"question":"称", "answers":[ "ショウ", "あげる", "かなう", "たたえる", "となえる", "はかる" ] },
	{"question":"浸", "answers":[ "シン", "ひたす", "ひたる", "しみる", "つかる", "つく" ] },
	{"question":"振", "answers":[ "シン", "ふる", "ふるう", "ふれる", "すくう" ] },
	{"question":"陣", "answers":[ "ジン", "チン", "じんだて" ] },
	{"question":"扇", "answers":[ "セン", "おうぎ", "あおぐ", "おだてる" ] },
	{"question":"恥", "answers":[ "チ", "はじ", "はじらう", "はじる", "はずかしい" ] },
	{"question":"致", "answers":[ "チ", "いたす" ] },
	{"question":"途", "answers":[ "ト", "ズ", "みち" ] },
	{"question":"透", "answers":[ "トウ", "すかす", "すく", "すける", "とおる" ] },
	{"question":"唐", "answers":[ "トウ", "から", "もろこし" ] },
	{"question":"桃", "answers":[ "トウ", "もも" ] },
	{"question":"倒", "answers":[ "トウ", "たおす", "たおれる", "こける", "さかさま" ] },
	{"question":"胴", "answers":[ "ドウ", "トウ" ] },
	{"question":"悩", "answers":[ "ノウ", "なやます", "なやむ", "ドウ" ] },
	{"question":"般", "answers":[ "ハン", "たぐい", "めぐる" ] },
	{"question":"被", "answers":[ "ヒ", "こうむる", "おおう", "かずける", "かぶせる", "かぶる" ] },
	{"question":"疲", "answers":[ "ヒ", "つかれる", "つからす" ] },
	{"question":"浜", "answers":[ "ヒン", "はま", "ヒョウ", "ホウ" ] },
	{"question":"敏", "answers":[ "ビン", "さとい", "とし" ] },
	{"question":"浮", "answers":[ "フ", "うかぶ", "うかべる", "うかれる", "うく", "ブ", "フウ" ] },
	{"question":"捕", "answers":[ "ホ", "つかまえる", "つかまる", "とらえる", "とらわれる", "とる", "ブ" ] },
	{"question":"峰", "answers":[ "ホウ", "みね", "フ" ] },
	{"question":"砲", "answers":[ "ホウ", "おおづつ", "つつ" ] },
	{"question":"眠", "answers":[ "ミン", "ねむい", "ねむる", "ベン" ] },
	{"question":"娘", "answers":[ "むすめ", "ジョウ", "ニョウ", "こ" ] },
	{"question":"紋", "answers":[ "モン", "ブン", "あや" ] },
	{"question":"涙", "answers":[ "ルイ", "なみだ" ] },
	{"question":"烈", "answers":[ "レツ", "はげしい" ] },
	{"question":"恋", "answers":[ "レン", "こい", "こいしい", "こう" ] },
	{"question":"朗", "answers":[ "ロウ", "ほがらか", "あきらか", "たからか" ] },
	{"question":"悦", "answers":[ "エツ", "よろこぶ" ] },
	{"question":"宴", "answers":[ "エン", "うたげ", "たのしむ" ] },
	{"question":"華", "answers":[ "カ", "はな", "ケ", "ゲ", "しろい" ] },
	{"question":"既", "answers":[ "キ", "すでに" ] },
	{"question":"脅", "answers":[ "キョウ", "おどかす", "おどす", "おびやかす", "おびえる" ] },
	{"question":"倹", "answers":[ "ケン", "つづまやか", "つましい" ] },
	{"question":"悟", "answers":[ "ゴ", "さとる" ] },
	{"question":"娯", "answers":[ "ゴ", "たのしむ" ] },
	{"question":"疾", "answers":[ "シツ", "とく", "とし", "にくむ", "はやい", "やまい", "やましい", "やむ" ] },
	{"question":"殊", "answers":[ "シュ", "こと" ] },
	{"question":"徐", "answers":[ "ジョ", "おもむろ" ] },
	{"question":"辱", "answers":[ "ジョク", "はずかしめる", "ニク", "かたじけない", "はじ", "はずかしめ" ] },
	{"question":"粋", "answers":[ "スイ", "いき" ] },
	{"question":"衰", "answers":[ "スイ", "おとろえる", "サイ", "シ" ] },
	{"question":"隻", "answers":[ "セキ", "ひとつ" ] },
	{"question":"桑", "answers":[ "くわ", "ソウ" ] },
	{"question":"託", "answers":[ "タク", "かこつ", "かこつける", "ことづかる", "まかせる" ] },
	{"question":"畜", "answers":[ "チク", "キク", "かう", "たくわえる", "やしなう" ] },
	{"question":"哲", "answers":[ "テツ", "あきらか", "さとい" ] },
	{"question":"凍", "answers":[ "トウ", "こおる", "こごえる", "いてる", "しみる" ] },
	{"question":"匿", "answers":[ "トク", "ジョク", "かくまう", "かくれる" ] },
	{"question":"畔", "answers":[ "ハン", "あぜ", "くろ", "そむく", "ほとり" ] },
	{"question":"姫", "answers":[ "ひめ", "キ" ] },
	{"question":"紛", "answers":[ "フン", "まぎらす", "まぎらわしい", "まぎらわす", "まぎれる", "まがう", "まぐれ", "みだれる" ] },
	{"question":"倣", "answers":[ "ホウ", "ならう" ] },
	{"question":"埋", "answers":[ "マイ", "うまる", "うめる", "うもれる", "いける", "うずまる", "うずもれる" ] },
	{"question":"浪", "answers":[ "ロウ", "ラン", "なみ", "みだりに" ] },
	{"question":"翁", "answers":[ "オウ", "おきな" ] },
	{"question":"蚊", "answers":[ "か", "ブン" ] },
	{"question":"核", "answers":[ "カク", "さね" ] },
	{"question":"陥", "answers":[ "カン", "おちいる", "おとしいれる" ] },
	{"question":"飢", "answers":[ "キ", "うえる", "うえ" ] },
	{"question":"恭", "answers":[ "キョウ", "うやうやしい", "つつしむ" ] },
	{"question":"貢", "answers":[ "コウ", "ク", "みつぐ" ] },
	{"question":"剛", "answers":[ "ゴウ", "コウ", "かたい", "つよい" ] },
	{"question":"唆", "answers":[ "サ", "そそのかす" ] },
	{"question":"栽", "answers":[ "サイ", "うえる" ] },
	{"question":"宰", "answers":[ "サイ", "つかさどる" ] },
	{"question":"索", "answers":[ "サク", "さがす", "つな", "なわ", "もとめる" ] },
	{"question":"桟", "answers":[ "サン", "かけはし", "たな" ] },
	{"question":"酌", "answers":[ "シャク", "くむ" ] },
	{"question":"珠", "answers":[ "シュ", "たま" ] },
	{"question":"准", "answers":[ "ジュン", "シュン", "なぞらえる", "ゆるす" ] },
	{"question":"殉", "answers":[ "ジュン", "したがう" ] },
	{"question":"祥", "answers":[ "ショウ", "きざし", "さいわい", "さち" ] },
	{"question":"症", "answers":[ "ショウ", "しるし" ] },
	{"question":"宵", "answers":[ "よい", "ショウ" ] },
	{"question":"娠", "answers":[ "シン", "はらむ", "みごもる" ] },
	{"question":"唇", "answers":[ "くちびる", "シン" ] },
	{"question":"畝", "answers":[ "うね", "ホ", "ボウ", "せ" ] },
	{"question":"逝", "answers":[ "セイ", "いく", "ゆく" ] },
	{"question":"栓", "answers":[ "セン" ] },
	{"question":"租", "answers":[ "ソ", "ちんがり", "みつぎ" ] },
	{"question":"捜", "answers":[ "ソウ", "さがす" ] },
	{"question":"挿", "answers":[ "ソウ", "さす", "さしはさむ", "すげる", "はさむ" ] },
	{"question":"泰", "answers":[ "タイ", "おごる", "やすい", "やすらか" ] },
	{"question":"逐", "answers":[ "チク", "ジク", "おう" ] },
	{"question":"秩", "answers":[ "チツ", "ついで", "ふち" ] },
	{"question":"朕", "answers":[ "チン", "きざし", "われ" ] },
	{"question":"逓", "answers":[ "テイ", "かわる", "たがいに" ] },
	{"question":"浦", "answers":[ "うら", "ホ" ] },
	{"question":"俸", "answers":[ "ホウ", "ふち" ] },
	{"question":"剖", "answers":[ "ボウ", "ホウ", "さく", "わける" ] },
	{"question":"紡", "answers":[ "ボウ", "つむぐ", "ホウ" ] },
	{"question":"耗", "answers":[ "モウ", "コウ", "ボウ", "たより", "へる" ] },
	{"question":"竜", "answers":[ "リュウ", "たつ", "リョウ", "リン" ] },
	{"question":"倫", "answers":[ "リン", "たぐい", "ついで", "みち" ] },
	{"question":"挨", "answers":[ "アイ", "おす", "ひらく" ] },
	{"question":"唄", "answers":[ "うた", "ハイ", "バイ", "うたう" ] },
	{"question":"俺", "answers":[ "おれ", "エン", "われ" ] },
	{"question":"釜", "answers":[ "かま", "フ" ] },
	{"question":"桁", "answers":[ "けた", "コウ", "かせ" ] },
	{"question":"拳", "answers":[ "ケン", "こぶし", "ゲン" ] },
	{"question":"挫", "answers":[ "ザ", "くじく", "くじける" ] },
	{"question":"恣", "answers":[ "シ", "ほしいまま" ] },
	{"question":"袖", "answers":[ "そで", "シュウ" ] },
	{"question":"凄", "answers":[ "セイ", "さむい", "すごい", "すごむ", "すさまじい" ] },
	{"question":"脊", "answers":[ "セキ", "せ", "せい" ] },
	{"question":"捉", "answers":[ "ソク", "とらえる", "つかまえる", "とる" ] },
	{"question":"酎", "answers":[ "チュウ" ] },
	{"question":"捗", "answers":[ "チョク", "はかどる" ] },
	{"question":"哺", "answers":[ "ホ", "はぐくむ", "ふくむ" ] },
	{"question":"冥", "answers":[ "メイ", "ミョウ", "くらい" ] },
	{"question":"脇", "answers":[ "わき", "キョウ", "かたわら" ] },
	{"question":"剝", "answers":[ "ハク", "はがす", "はがれる", "はぐ", "はげる", "ホク", "とる", "むく" ] },
	{"question":"魚", "answers":[ "ギョ", "うお", "さかな" ] },
	{"question":"教", "answers":[ "キョウ", "おしえる", "おそわる" ] },
	{"question":"強", "answers":[ "キョウ", "つよい", "つよまる", "つよめる", "ゴウ", "しいる", "あながち", "こわい", "したたか", "つとめる" ] },
	{"question":"黄", "answers":[ "オウ", "き", "コウ", "こ" ] },
	{"question":"黒", "answers":[ "コク", "くろ", "くろい" ] },
	{"question":"細", "answers":[ "サイ", "こまか", "こまかい", "ほそい", "ほそる", "くわしい", "ささやか" ] },
	{"question":"週", "answers":[ "シュウ", "めぐる" ] },
	{"question":"雪", "answers":[ "セツ", "ゆき", "すすぐ", "そそぐ" ] },
	{"question":"船", "answers":[ "セン", "ふな", "ふね" ] },
	{"question":"組", "answers":[ "ソ", "くみ", "くむ", "くみひも" ] },
	{"question":"鳥", "answers":[ "チョウ", "とり" ] },
	{"question":"野", "answers":[ "ヤ", "の", "ショ", "いなかや", "いやしい" ] },
	{"question":"理", "answers":[ "リ", "おさめる", "ことわり", "すじ" ] },
	{"question":"悪", "answers":[ "アク", "わるい", "オ", "あし", "いずくんぞ", "にくむ" ] },
	{"question":"球", "answers":[ "キュウ", "たま" ] },
	{"question":"祭", "answers":[ "サイ", "まつり", "まつる" ] },
	{"question":"習", "answers":[ "シュウ", "ならう", "ジュウ" ] },
	{"question":"終", "answers":[ "シュウ", "おえる", "おわる", "しまう", "ついに" ] },
	{"question":"宿", "answers":[ "シュク", "やど", "やどす", "やどる", "シュウ", "スク" ] },
	{"question":"章", "answers":[ "ショウ", "あや", "しるし", "ふみ" ] },
	{"question":"商", "answers":[ "ショウ", "あきなう", "あきない", "はかる" ] },
	{"question":"進", "answers":[ "シン", "すすむ", "すすめる" ] },
	{"question":"深", "answers":[ "シン", "ふかい", "ふかまる", "ふかめる", "ふける", "み" ] },
	{"question":"族", "answers":[ "ゾク", "やから" ] },
	{"question":"第", "answers":[ "ダイ", "テイ", "ついで", "やしき" ] },
	{"question":"帳", "answers":[ "チョウ", "とばり", "はり" ] },
	{"question":"笛", "answers":[ "テキ", "ふえ", "ジャク" ] },
	{"question":"転", "answers":[ "テン", "ころがす", "ころがる", "ころげる", "ころぶ", "うたた", "うつる", "くるり", "こける", "まろぶ" ] },
	{"question":"都", "answers":[ "ツ", "ト", "みやこ", "すべて" ] },
	{"question":"動", "answers":[ "ドウ", "うごかす", "うごく", "トウ", "ややもすれば" ] },
	{"question":"部", "answers":[ "ブ", "ホ", "ホウ", "くみ", "すべる", "つかさ", "べ", "わける" ] },
	{"question":"問", "answers":[ "モン", "とい", "とう", "とん", "ブン", "たずねる", "たより" ] },
	{"question":"貨", "answers":[ "カ", "たから" ] },
	{"question":"械", "answers":[ "カイ", "かせ", "からくり" ] },
	{"question":"救", "answers":[ "キュウ", "すくう", "ク", "グ", "たすける" ] },
	{"question":"健", "answers":[ "ケン", "すこやか", "したたか", "たけし" ] },
	{"question":"康", "answers":[ "コウ", "やすい" ] },
	{"question":"菜", "answers":[ "サイ", "な" ] },
	{"question":"産", "answers":[ "サン", "うまれる", "うむ", "うぶ" ] },
	{"question":"唱", "answers":[ "ショウ", "となえる", "うた", "うたう" ] },
	{"question":"清", "answers":[ "セイ", "きよい", "きよまる", "きよめる", "ショウ", "シン", "さやか", "すむ" ] },
	{"question":"巣", "answers":[ "す", "ソウ" ] },
	{"question":"側", "answers":[ "ソク", "がわ", "ショク", "かたわら", "かわ", "そば", "はた" ] },
	{"question":"停", "answers":[ "テイ", "とどまる", "とまる" ] },
	{"question":"堂", "answers":[ "ドウ", "トウ", "たかどの" ] },
	{"question":"得", "answers":[ "トク", "える", "うる" ] },
	{"question":"敗", "answers":[ "ハイ", "やぶれる", "まける", "やぶる" ] },
	{"question":"票", "answers":[ "ヒョウ", "ふだ" ] },
	{"question":"副", "answers":[ "フク", "フウ", "そう" ] },
	{"question":"望", "answers":[ "ボウ", "のぞむ", "モウ", "うらむ", "もち" ] },
	{"question":"陸", "answers":[ "リク", "ロク", "おか", "くが" ] },
	{"question":"移", "answers":[ "イ", "うつす", "うつる" ] },
	{"question":"液", "answers":[ "エキ", "しる", "わき" ] },
	{"question":"眼", "answers":[ "ガン", "まなこ", "ゲン", "め" ] },
	{"question":"規", "answers":[ "キ", "ただす", "のり", "ぶんまわし" ] },
	{"question":"基", "answers":[ "キ", "もと", "もとい", "もとづく" ] },
	{"question":"寄", "answers":[ "キ", "よせる", "よる" ] },
	{"question":"許", "answers":[ "キョ", "ゆるす", "コ", "ばかり", "もと" ] },
	{"question":"経", "answers":[ "ケイ", "へる", "キョウ", "キン", "おさめる", "たつ", "たていと" ] },
	{"question":"険", "answers":[ "ケン", "けわしい" ] },
	{"question":"現", "answers":[ "ゲン", "あらわす", "あらわれる", "うつつ" ] },
	{"question":"混", "answers":[ "コン", "こむ", "まざる", "まじる", "まぜる" ] },
	{"question":"採", "answers":[ "サイ", "とる" ] },
	{"question":"授", "answers":[ "ジュ", "さずかる", "さずける" ] },
	{"question":"術", "answers":[ "ジュツ", "シュツ", "スイ", "すべ", "わざ" ] },
	{"question":"常", "answers":[ "ジョウ", "つね", "とこ" ] },
	{"question":"情", "answers":[ "ジョウ", "なさけ", "セイ", "おもむき", "こころ" ] },
	{"question":"責", "answers":[ "セキ", "せめる", "サイ", "シャク" ] },
	{"question":"設", "answers":[ "セツ", "もうける", "セチ", "しつらえる", "たとい", "もし" ] },
	{"question":"接", "answers":[ "セツ", "つぐ", "ショウ", "はぐ", "まじわる", "もてなす" ] },
	{"question":"断", "answers":[ "ダン", "ことわる", "たつ", "さだめる" ] },
	{"question":"張", "answers":[ "チョウ", "はる" ] },
	{"question":"貧", "answers":[ "ビン", "まずしい", "ヒン" ] },
	{"question":"婦", "answers":[ "フ", "おんな" ] },
	{"question":"務", "answers":[ "ム", "つとまる", "つとめる", "ブ", "あなどり", "あなどる", "つとめ" ] },
	{"question":"率", "answers":[ "リツ", "ひきいる", "ソツ", "シュツ", "スイ", "おおむね", "かしら", "したがう", "わりあい" ] },
	{"question":"略", "answers":[ "リャク", "おかす", "おさめる", "はかりごと", "はかる", "はぶく", "ほぼ" ] },
	{"question":"異", "answers":[ "イ", "こと", "あやしい" ] },
	{"question":"域", "answers":[ "イキ", "ヨク", "さかい", "ところ" ] },
	{"question":"郷", "answers":[ "キョウ", "ゴウ", "さと" ] },
	{"question":"済", "answers":[ "サイ", "すます", "すむ", "セイ", "すくう", "なす", "わたす", "わたる" ] },
	{"question":"視", "answers":[ "シ", "みる" ] },
	{"question":"捨", "answers":[ "シャ", "すてる", "ほどこす" ] },
	{"question":"推", "answers":[ "スイ", "おす" ] },
	{"question":"盛", "answers":[ "もる", "セイ", "さかる", "さかん", "ジョウ" ] },
	{"question":"窓", "answers":[ "ソウ", "まど" ] },
	{"question":"探", "answers":[ "タン", "さがす", "さぐる" ] },
	{"question":"著", "answers":[ "チョ", "あらわす", "いちじるしい", "ジャク", "チャク", "きる", "つく" ] },
	{"question":"頂", "answers":[ "チョウ", "いただき", "いただく", "テイ" ] },
	{"question":"脳", "answers":[ "ノウ", "ドウ" ] },
	{"question":"閉", "answers":[ "ヘイ", "しまる", "しめる", "とじる", "とざす", "たてる" ] },
	{"question":"訪", "answers":[ "ホウ", "たずねる", "おとずれる", "おとなう", "とう" ] },
	{"question":"密", "answers":[ "ミツ", "ビツ", "こまかい", "ひそかに" ] },
	{"question":"訳", "answers":[ "ヤク", "わけ", "エキ", "とく" ] },
	{"question":"郵", "answers":[ "ユウ", "しゅくば" ] },
	{"question":"翌", "answers":[ "ヨク" ] },
	{"question":"欲", "answers":[ "ヨク", "ほしい", "ほっする" ] },
	{"question":"陰", "answers":[ "イン", "かげ", "かげる", "アン", "オン", "くもる", "くらい", "ひそか" ] },
	{"question":"菓", "answers":[ "カ", "くだもの" ] },
	{"question":"乾", "answers":[ "カン", "かわかす", "かわく", "ケン", "いぬい", "ひ", "ほす" ] },
	{"question":"脚", "answers":[ "キャク", "あし", "キャ", "カク" ] },
	{"question":"掘", "answers":[ "クツ", "ほる" ] },
	{"question":"婚", "answers":[ "コン" ] },
	{"question":"彩", "answers":[ "サイ", "いろどる", "あや" ] },
	{"question":"惨", "answers":[ "サン", "ザン", "みじめ", "いたましい", "いたむ", "むごい" ] },
	{"question":"執", "answers":[ "シツ", "シュウ", "とる", "とらえる" ] },
	{"question":"斜", "answers":[ "シャ", "ななめ", "はす" ] },
	{"question":"釈", "answers":[ "シャク", "セキ", "おく", "とかす", "とく", "ゆるす" ] },
	{"question":"寂", "answers":[ "ジャク", "さび", "さびしい", "さびれる", "セキ", "さびる", "しずか" ] },
	{"question":"紹", "answers":[ "ショウ", "つぐ" ] },
	{"question":"脱", "answers":[ "ダツ", "ぬぐ", "ぬげる", "タイ", "タツ" ] },
	{"question":"淡", "answers":[ "タン", "あわい", "うすい" ] },
	{"question":"添", "answers":[ "テン", "そう", "そえる" ] },
	{"question":"盗", "answers":[ "トウ", "ぬすむ", "とる" ] },
	{"question":"販", "answers":[ "ハン", "あきなう", "ひさぐ" ] },
	{"question":"描", "answers":[ "ビョウ", "えがく", "かく" ] },
	{"question":"猛", "answers":[ "モウ", "たけし" ] },
	{"question":"粒", "answers":[ "リュウ", "つぶ" ] },
	{"question":"郭", "answers":[ "カク", "くるわ" ] },
	{"question":"掛", "answers":[ "かかり", "かかる", "かける" ] },
	{"question":"勘", "answers":[ "カン", "かんがえる" ] },
	{"question":"貫", "answers":[ "カン", "つらぬく", "ワン", "ぬき", "ぬく", "ひく" ] },
	{"question":"菊", "answers":[ "キク" ] },
	{"question":"虚", "answers":[ "キョ", "コ", "うつける", "うつろ", "うろ", "むなしい" ] },
	{"question":"偶", "answers":[ "グウ", "たぐい", "たまたま", "ひとがた" ] },
	{"question":"啓", "answers":[ "ケイ", "ひらく", "もうす" ] },
	{"question":"掲", "answers":[ "ケイ", "かかげる" ] },
	{"question":"控", "answers":[ "ひかえる", "コウ", "つげる", "のぞく" ] },
	{"question":"紺", "answers":[ "コン" ] },
	{"question":"赦", "answers":[ "シャ", "ゆるす" ] },
	{"question":"酔", "answers":[ "スイ", "よう" ] },
	{"question":"惜", "answers":[ "セキ", "おしい", "おしむ", "シャク" ] },
	{"question":"措", "answers":[ "ソ", "サク", "おく", "はからう" ] },
	{"question":"粗", "answers":[ "ソ", "あらい", "ほぼ" ] },
	{"question":"掃", "answers":[ "ソウ", "はく", "はらう" ] },
	{"question":"逮", "answers":[ "タイ", "テイ", "およぶ", "とらえる" ] },
	{"question":"袋", "answers":[ "ふくろ", "タイ", "テイ" ] },
	{"question":"窒", "answers":[ "チツ", "ふさがる" ] },
	{"question":"彫", "answers":[ "チョウ", "ほる" ] },
	{"question":"陳", "answers":[ "チン", "ジン", "つらねる", "のべる", "ひねる", "ふるい" ] },
	{"question":"陶", "answers":[ "トウ", "ヨウ", "すえ" ] },
	{"question":"豚", "answers":[ "トン", "ぶた" ] },
	{"question":"粘", "answers":[ "ネン", "ねばる", "デン" ] },
	{"question":"婆", "answers":[ "バ", "ばば" ] },
	{"question":"排", "answers":[ "ハイ", "おしのける", "つらねる" ] },
	{"question":"陪", "answers":[ "バイ", "したがう" ] },
	{"question":"符", "answers":[ "フ", "わりふ" ] },
	{"question":"崩", "answers":[ "ホウ", "くずす", "くずれる" ] },
	{"question":"隆", "answers":[ "リュウ", "さかん", "たかい" ] },
	{"question":"猟", "answers":[ "リョウ", "かり", "かる" ] },
	{"question":"陵", "answers":[ "リョウ", "みささぎ", "おか", "しのぐ" ] },
	{"question":"尉", "answers":[ "イ", "ウツ", "じょう" ] },
	{"question":"逸", "answers":[ "イツ", "イチ", "うしなう", "すぐれる", "そらす", "それる", "はぐれる", "はしる", "はやる" ] },
	{"question":"涯", "answers":[ "ガイ", "はて", "みぎわ" ] },
	{"question":"殻", "answers":[ "カク", "から" ] },
	{"question":"喝", "answers":[ "カツ", "おどす", "しかる" ] },
	{"question":"渇", "answers":[ "かわく", "カツ", "ケツ", "むさぼる" ] },
	{"question":"患", "answers":[ "カン", "わずらう", "ゲン", "うれい", "うれえる", "わずらい" ] },
	{"question":"偽", "answers":[ "ギ", "いつわる", "にせ" ] },
	{"question":"菌", "answers":[ "キン", "きのこ", "たけ" ] },
	{"question":"蛍", "answers":[ "ケイ", "ほたる" ] },
	{"question":"渓", "answers":[ "ケイ", "たに" ] },
	{"question":"斎", "answers":[ "サイ", "いつく", "つつしむ", "とき", "ものいみ" ] },
	{"question":"崎", "answers":[ "さき", "キ" ] },
	{"question":"蛇", "answers":[ "ジャ", "ダ", "へび", "イ", "タ" ] },
	{"question":"渋", "answers":[ "ジュウ", "しぶ", "しぶい", "しぶる", "シュウ" ] },
	{"question":"粛", "answers":[ "シュク", "つつしむ" ] },
	{"question":"淑", "answers":[ "シュク", "しとやか", "よい" ] },
	{"question":"庶", "answers":[ "ショ", "おおい", "こいねがう", "もろもろ" ] },
	{"question":"渉", "answers":[ "ショウ", "かかわる", "わたる" ] },
	{"question":"訟", "answers":[ "ショウ", "ジュ", "うったえ", "うったえる" ] },
	{"question":"剰", "answers":[ "ジョウ", "あます", "あまつさえ", "あまる" ] },
	{"question":"紳", "answers":[ "シン", "おおおび" ] },
	{"question":"崇", "answers":[ "スウ", "シュウ", "あがめる", "おわる", "たかい", "たっとぶ", "とうとぶ" ] },
	{"question":"据", "answers":[ "すえる", "すわる", "キョ" ] },
	{"question":"旋", "answers":[ "セン", "めぐる" ] },
	{"question":"曹", "answers":[ "ソウ", "ゾウ", "つかさ", "ともがら" ] },
	{"question":"眺", "answers":[ "チョウ", "ながめる" ] },
	{"question":"釣", "answers":[ "つる", "チョウ" ] },
	{"question":"偵", "answers":[ "テイ", "うかがう" ] },
	{"question":"悼", "answers":[ "トウ", "いたむ" ] },
	{"question":"軟", "answers":[ "ナン", "やわらか", "やわらかい", "ゼン", "ネン" ] },
	{"question":"培", "answers":[ "バイ", "つちかう", "ハイ", "ホウ", "おか" ] },
	{"question":"舶", "answers":[ "ハク", "おおぶね" ] },
	{"question":"猫", "answers":[ "ねこ", "ビョウ", "ミョウ" ] },
	{"question":"瓶", "answers":[ "ビン", "ヘイ", "かめ" ] },
	{"question":"偏", "answers":[ "ヘン", "かたよる", "ひとえに" ] },
	{"question":"堀", "answers":[ "ほり", "クツ", "コツ", "あな" ] },
	{"question":"麻", "answers":[ "マ", "あさ", "バ", "しびれる" ] },
	{"question":"唯", "answers":[ "ユイ", "イ", "ただ" ] },
	{"question":"悠", "answers":[ "ユウ", "とおい", "はるか" ] },
	{"question":"庸", "answers":[ "ヨウ", "おろか", "つね", "なんぞ", "もちいる" ] },
	{"question":"涼", "answers":[ "リョウ", "すずしい", "すずむ", "うすい" ] },
	{"question":"累", "answers":[ "ルイ", "かさなる", "かさねる", "しきりに", "しばる", "わずらわす" ] },
	{"question":"萎", "answers":[ "イ", "なえる", "しおれる", "しなびる", "しぼむ", "つかれる" ] },
	{"question":"淫", "answers":[ "イン", "みだら", "あふれる", "おおきい", "ながあめ", "ふける", "ほしいまま", "みだす", "みだら" ] },
	{"question":"崖", "answers":[ "ガイ", "がけ", "かどだつ" ] },
	{"question":"亀", "answers":[ "キ", "かめ", "キュウ", "キン", "あかぎれ" ] },
	{"question":"惧", "answers":[ "グ", "ク", "おそれる" ] },
	{"question":"舷", "answers":[ "ゲン", "ふなばた", "ふなべり" ] },
	{"question":"梗", "answers":[ "コウ", "キョウ", "おおむね", "かたい", "つよい", "でく", "ふさがる" ] },
	{"question":"頃", "answers":[ "ころ", "キ", "キョウ", "ケイ", "かたあし", "しばらく" ] },
	{"question":"痕", "answers":[ "コン", "あと" ] },
	{"question":"埼", "answers":[ "さい", "キ", "さき" ] },
	{"question":"斬", "answers":[ "ザン", "きる", "サン" ] },
	{"question":"鹿", "answers":[ "か", "しか", "ロク" ] },
	{"question":"羞", "answers":[ "シュウ", "すすめる", "はじ", "はじる", "はずかしめ", "はずかしめる" ] },
	{"question":"戚", "answers":[ "セキ", "いたむ", "うれえる", "みうち" ] },
	{"question":"曽", "answers":[ "ゾ", "ソウ", "ソ", "ゾウ", "かさなる", "かつて", "すなわち", "ます" ] },
	{"question":"爽", "answers":[ "ソウ", "さわやか", "ショウ", "あきらか", "たがう" ] },
	{"question":"唾", "answers":[ "ダ", "つば", "タ", "つばき" ] },
	{"question":"堆", "answers":[ "タイ", "ツイ", "うずたかい" ] },
	{"question":"貪", "answers":[ "ドン", "むさぼる", "タン" ] },
	{"question":"梨", "answers":[ "なし", "リ" ] },
	{"question":"捻", "answers":[ "ネン", "デン", "ねじる", "ひねる" ] },
	{"question":"森", "answers":[ "シン", "もり" ] },
	{"question":"雲", "answers":[ "ウン", "くも", "そら" ] },
	{"question":"絵", "answers":[ "エ", "カイ", "えがく" ] },
	{"question":"間", "answers":[ "カン", "ケン", "あいだ", "ま", "あい", "うかがう", "しずか", "はざま", "ひそかに" ] },
	{"question":"場", "answers":[ "ジョウ", "ば" ] },
	{"question":"晴", "answers":[ "セイ", "はらす", "はれる" ] },
	{"question":"朝", "answers":[ "チョウ", "あさ", "あした" ] },
	{"question":"答", "answers":[ "トウ", "こたえ", "こたえる" ] },
	{"question":"道", "answers":[ "ドウ", "みち", "トウ", "いう", "みちびく" ] },
	{"question":"買", "answers":[ "バイ", "かう" ] },
	{"question":"番", "answers":[ "バン", "ハ", "ハン", "つがい", "つがう", "つがえる" ] },
	{"question":"飲", "answers":[ "イン", "のむ", "オン", "のます", "みずかう" ] },
	{"question":"運", "answers":[ "ウン", "はこぶ", "さだめ", "めぐる" ] },
	{"question":"温", "answers":[ "オン", "あたたか", "あたたかい", "あたたまる", "あたためる", "ウン", "たずねる", "つつむ", "ぬくい", "ぬくまる", "ぬくめる", "ぬるい" ] },
	{"question":"開", "answers":[ "カイ", "あく", "あける", "ひらく", "ひらける", "はだかる", "はだける" ] },
	{"question":"階", "answers":[ "カイ", "きざはし", "しな", "はしご" ] },
	{"question":"寒", "answers":[ "カン", "さむい", "いやしい", "さびしい", "まずしい" ] },
	{"question":"期", "answers":[ "キ", "ゴ", "きめる", "ちぎる", "とき" ] },
	{"question":"軽", "answers":[ "ケイ", "かるい", "かろやか", "キン" ] },
	{"question":"湖", "answers":[ "コ", "みずうみ" ] },
	{"question":"港", "answers":[ "コウ", "みなと" ] },
	{"question":"歯", "answers":[ "シ", "は", "よわい" ] },
	{"question":"集", "answers":[ "シュウ", "あつまる", "あつめる", "つどう", "すだく", "たかる" ] },
	{"question":"暑", "answers":[ "ショ", "あつい" ] },
	{"question":"勝", "answers":[ "ショウ", "かつ", "まさる", "すぐれる", "たえる" ] },
	{"question":"植", "answers":[ "ショク", "うえる", "うわる", "チ", "たてる" ] },
	{"question":"短", "answers":[ "タン", "みじかい" ] },
	{"question":"着", "answers":[ "チャク", "きせる", "きる", "つく", "つける", "ジャク" ] },
	{"question":"等", "answers":[ "トウ", "ひとしい", "など", "ら" ] },
	{"question":"登", "answers":[ "ト", "トウ", "のぼる" ] },
	{"question":"湯", "answers":[ "トウ", "ゆ", "ショウ" ] },
	{"question":"童", "answers":[ "ドウ", "わらべ", "トウ", "わらわ" ] },
	{"question":"悲", "answers":[ "ヒ", "かなしい", "かなしむ" ] },
	{"question":"筆", "answers":[ "ヒツ", "ふで" ] },
	{"question":"遊", "answers":[ "ユウ", "あそぶ", "ユ", "すさび", "すさぶ" ] },
	{"question":"葉", "answers":[ "ヨウ", "は", "ショウ", "かみ", "すえ" ] },
	{"question":"陽", "answers":[ "ヨウ", "いつわる", "ひ", "ひなた" ] },
	{"question":"落", "answers":[ "ラク", "おちる", "おとす", "さと" ] },
	{"question":"街", "answers":[ "ガイ", "まち", "カイ", "ちまた" ] },
	{"question":"覚", "answers":[ "カク", "おぼえる", "さます", "さめる", "コウ", "さとり", "さとる" ] },
	{"question":"喜", "answers":[ "キ", "よろこぶ" ] },
	{"question":"給", "answers":[ "キュウ", "たまう", "たまわる" ] },
	{"question":"極", "answers":[ "キョク", "ゴク", "きわまる", "きわみ", "きわめる", "きまる", "きめる" ] },
	{"question":"景", "answers":[ "ケイ", "エイ" ] },
	{"question":"結", "answers":[ "ケツ", "むすぶ", "ゆう", "ゆわえる", "ケイ", "ケチ", "すく" ] },
	{"question":"最", "answers":[ "サイ", "もっとも", "も" ] },
	{"question":"散", "answers":[ "サン", "ちらかす", "ちらかる", "ちらす", "ちる", "ばら" ] },
	{"question":"順", "answers":[ "ジュン", "したがう", "すなお" ] },
	{"question":"焼", "answers":[ "やく", "やける", "ショウ", "くべる" ] },
	{"question":"象", "answers":[ "ショウ", "ゾウ", "かたち", "かたどる" ] },
	{"question":"隊", "answers":[ "タイ", "ツイ", "おちる", "くみ" ] },
	{"question":"達", "answers":[ "タツ", "タチ", "ダチ", "たし", "たち", "とおる", "とどく" ] },
	{"question":"貯", "answers":[ "チョ", "たくわえる" ] },
	{"question":"然", "answers":[ "ゼン", "ネン", "しかし", "しかして", "しかも", "しからば", "しかり", "もえる" ] },
	{"question":"博", "answers":[ "ハク", "バク", "ひろい", "ひろめる" ] },
	{"question":"飯", "answers":[ "ハン", "めし", "いい", "くらう", "まま" ] },
	{"question":"費", "answers":[ "ヒ", "ついえる", "ついやす" ] },
	{"question":"無", "answers":[ "ブ", "ム", "ない" ] },
	{"question":"満", "answers":[ "マン", "みたす", "みちる", "バン" ] },
	{"question":"量", "answers":[ "リョウ", "はかる", "かさ", "ちから" ] },
	{"question":"営", "answers":[ "エイ", "いとなむ", "ヨウ" ] },
	{"question":"過", "answers":[ "カ", "すぎる", "すごす", "あやまち", "あやまつ", "とが", "よぎる" ] },
	{"question":"賀", "answers":[ "ガ", "よろこぶ" ] },
	{"question":"検", "answers":[ "ケン", "あらためる", "しらべる" ] },
	{"question":"減", "answers":[ "ゲン", "へらす", "へる" ] },
	{"question":"証", "answers":[ "ショウ", "あかし", "あかし", "あかす" ] },
	{"question":"税", "answers":[ "ゼイ", "セイ", "みつぎ" ] },
	{"question":"絶", "answers":[ "ゼツ", "たえる", "たつ", "たやす", "ゼチ", "セツ", "はなはだ", "わたる" ] },
	{"question":"測", "answers":[ "ソク", "はかる" ] },
	{"question":"属", "answers":[ "ゾク", "ショク", "つく", "やから" ] },
	{"question":"貸", "answers":[ "かす", "タイ" ] },
	{"question":"程", "answers":[ "テイ", "ほど", "のり" ] },
	{"question":"提", "answers":[ "テイ", "さげる", "ダイ", "チョウ", "ひさげ", "ひっさげる" ] },
	{"question":"統", "answers":[ "トウ", "すべる", "おさめる", "すじ" ] },
	{"question":"備", "answers":[ "ビ", "そなえる", "そなわる", "ヒ", "つぶさに" ] },
	{"question":"評", "answers":[ "ヒョウ", "ヘイ", "あげつらう", "はかる" ] },
	{"question":"富", "answers":[ "フ", "とみ", "とむ", "フウ" ] },
	{"question":"復", "answers":[ "フク", "かえす", "かえる", "ふたたび", "また" ] },
	{"question":"報", "answers":[ "ホウ", "むくいる", "しらせる" ] },
	{"question":"割", "answers":[ "わり", "わる", "われる", "カツ", "さく" ] },
	{"question":"揮", "answers":[ "キ", "ふるう" ] },
	{"question":"貴", "answers":[ "キ", "たっとい", "たっとぶ", "とうとい", "とうとぶ", "たかい" ] },
	{"question":"筋", "answers":[ "キン", "すじ" ] },
	{"question":"勤", "answers":[ "キン", "つとまる", "つとめる", "ゴン", "いそしむ", "つとめ" ] },
	{"question":"敬", "answers":[ "ケイ", "うやまう", "キョウ", "つつしむ" ] },
	{"question":"裁", "answers":[ "サイ", "さばく", "たつ" ] },
	{"question":"策", "answers":[ "サク", "つえ", "はかりごと", "ふだ", "むち" ] },
	{"question":"詞", "answers":[ "シ", "ことば" ] },
	{"question":"衆", "answers":[ "シュウ", "シュ", "おおい" ] },
	{"question":"就", "answers":[ "シュウ", "つく", "つける", "ジュ", "なす", "なる" ] },
	{"question":"善", "answers":[ "ゼン", "よい", "セン" ] },
	{"question":"装", "answers":[ "ソウ", "ショウ", "よそおう", "よそう" ] },
	{"question":"創", "answers":[ "ソウ", "つくる", "きず", "はじめる" ] },
	{"question":"尊", "answers":[ "ソン", "たっとい", "たっとぶ", "とうとい", "とうとぶ", "みこと" ] },
	{"question":"痛", "answers":[ "ツウ", "いたい", "いたむ", "いためる", "トウ", "いたわしい", "やめる" ] },
	{"question":"晩", "answers":[ "バン", "おそい", "くれ" ] },
	{"question":"補", "answers":[ "ホ", "おぎなう", "フ", "たすける" ] },
	{"question":"棒", "answers":[ "ボウ", "ホウ" ] },
	{"question":"握", "answers":[ "アク", "にぎる" ] },
	{"question":"偉", "answers":[ "イ", "えらい", "すぐれる" ] },
	{"question":"越", "answers":[ "エツ", "こえる", "こす", "オチ", "オツ", "こし" ] },
	{"question":"援", "answers":[ "エン", "たすける", "ひく" ] },
	{"question":"奥", "answers":[ "おく", "オウ", "イク", "くま" ] },
	{"question":"幾", "answers":[ "キ", "いく", "きざし", "こいねがう", "ほとんど" ] },
	{"question":"距", "answers":[ "キョ", "けづめ", "ふせぐ", "へだてる" ] },
	{"question":"御", "answers":[ "ギョ", "ゴ", "おん", "お", "おさめる", "み" ] },
	{"question":"堅", "answers":[ "ケン", "かたい" ] },
	{"question":"圏", "answers":[ "ケン", "かこい" ] },
	{"question":"項", "answers":[ "コウ", "うなじ" ] },
	{"question":"紫", "answers":[ "シ", "むらさき" ] },
	{"question":"煮", "answers":[ "にえる", "にやす", "にる", "シャ" ] },
	{"question":"畳", "answers":[ "ジョウ", "たたみ", "たたむ", "チョウ", "かさなる", "かさねる" ] },
	{"question":"殖", "answers":[ "ショク", "ふえる", "ふやす" ] },
	{"question":"尋", "answers":[ "ジン", "たずねる", "つね", "ひろ" ] },
	{"question":"訴", "answers":[ "ソ", "うったえる" ] },
	{"question":"替", "answers":[ "タイ", "かえる", "かわる", "テイ" ] },
	{"question":"弾", "answers":[ "ダン", "たま", "はずむ", "ひく", "ただす", "はじく", "はじける", "はずみ" ] },
	{"question":"遅", "answers":[ "チ", "おくらす", "おくれる", "おそい" ] },
	{"question":"堤", "answers":[ "テイ", "つつみ" ] },
	{"question":"渡", "answers":[ "ト", "わたす", "わたる" ] },
	{"question":"塔", "answers":[ "トウ" ] },
	{"question":"鈍", "answers":[ "ドン", "にぶい", "にぶる", "トン", "なまる", "にび", "のろい" ] },
	{"question":"普", "answers":[ "フ", "あまねく" ] },
	{"question":"幅", "answers":[ "フク", "はば" ] },
	{"question":"傍", "answers":[ "ボウ", "かたわら", "ホウ", "そう", "そば", "はた", "わき" ] },
	{"question":"帽", "answers":[ "ボウ" ] },
	{"question":"雄", "answers":[ "ユウ", "お", "おす", "おん", "まさる" ] },
	{"question":"絡", "answers":[ "ラク", "からまる", "からむ", "からめる", "からげる", "つなぐ", "まとう" ] },
	{"question":"惑", "answers":[ "ワク", "まどう" ] },
	{"question":"腕", "answers":[ "ワン", "うで", "かいな" ] },
	{"question":"詠", "answers":[ "エイ", "よむ", "うたう", "ながめる" ] },
	{"question":"敢", "answers":[ "カン", "あえて" ] },
	{"question":"換", "answers":[ "カン", "かえる", "かわる" ] },
	{"question":"喚", "answers":[ "カン", "さけぶ", "よぶ", "わめく" ] },
	{"question":"棋", "answers":[ "キ", "ゴ" ] },
	{"question":"欺", "answers":[ "ギ", "あざむく", "キ" ] },
	{"question":"喫", "answers":[ "キツ", "くう", "すう", "のむ" ] },
	{"question":"遇", "answers":[ "グウ", "グ", "あう", "たまたま", "もてなす" ] },
	{"question":"雇", "answers":[ "コ", "やとう" ] },
	{"question":"硬", "answers":[ "コウ", "かたい" ] },
	{"question":"慌", "answers":[ "あわただしい", "あわてる", "コウ" ] },
	{"question":"絞", "answers":[ "しぼる", "しまる", "しめる", "コウ", "くびる" ] },
	{"question":"軸", "answers":[ "ジク", "チク", "しんぎ" ] },
	{"question":"湿", "answers":[ "シツ", "しめす", "しめる", "うるおい", "うるおす" ] },
	{"question":"晶", "answers":[ "ショウ", "あきらか" ] },
	{"question":"掌", "answers":[ "ショウ", "たなごころ", "つかさどる", "てのひら" ] },
	{"question":"焦", "answers":[ "ショウ", "こがす", "こがれる", "こげる", "あせる", "じらす", "じれる", "やく" ] },
	{"question":"遂", "answers":[ "スイ", "とげる", "おおせる", "ついに" ] },
	{"question":"随", "answers":[ "ズイ", "したがう" ] },
	{"question":"婿", "answers":[ "むこ", "セイ" ] },
	{"question":"葬", "answers":[ "ソウ", "ほうむる" ] },
	{"question":"超", "answers":[ "チョウ", "こえる", "こす" ] },
	{"question":"痘", "answers":[ "トウ", "もがさ" ] },
	{"question":"蛮", "answers":[ "バン", "えびす" ] },
	{"question":"募", "answers":[ "ボ", "つのる", "モ" ] },
	{"question":"揚", "answers":[ "ヨウ", "あがる", "あげる" ] },
	{"question":"揺", "answers":[ "ヨウ", "ゆさぶる", "ゆすぶる", "ゆする", "ゆらぐ", "ゆる", "ゆるぐ", "ゆれる" ] },
	{"question":"裂", "answers":[ "レツ", "さく", "さける", "きれ" ] },
	{"question":"廊", "answers":[ "ロウ", "わたどの" ] },
	{"question":"湾", "answers":[ "ワン", "いりえ" ] },
	{"question":"渦", "answers":[ "うず", "カ" ] },
	{"question":"棺", "answers":[ "カン", "ひつぎ" ] },
	{"question":"堪", "answers":[ "たえる", "カン", "タン", "こたえる", "こらえる", "たまる" ] },
	{"question":"款", "answers":[ "カン", "しるす", "たたく", "まこと", "よろこぶ" ] },
	{"question":"閑", "answers":[ "カン", "しずか", "ならう", "ひま" ] },
	{"question":"暁", "answers":[ "あかつき", "ギョウ", "さとる" ] },
	{"question":"琴", "answers":[ "キン", "こと", "ゴン" ] },
	{"question":"隅", "answers":[ "グウ", "すみ" ] },
	{"question":"詐", "answers":[ "サ", "あざむく", "いつわり", "いつわる" ] },
	{"question":"酢", "answers":[ "サク", "す", "ソ", "すい" ] },
	{"question":"傘", "answers":[ "かさ", "サン" ] },
	{"question":"滋", "answers":[ "ジ", "シ", "しげる", "ます" ] },
	{"question":"循", "answers":[ "ジュン", "したがう", "めぐる" ] },
	{"question":"硝", "answers":[ "ショウ" ] },
	{"question":"粧", "answers":[ "ショウ", "ソウ", "めかす", "よそおう" ] },
	{"question":"詔", "answers":[ "ショウ", "みことのり", "つげる" ] },
	{"question":"診", "answers":[ "シン", "みる" ] },
	{"question":"疎", "answers":[ "ソ", "うとい", "うとむ", "ショ", "うろ", "おろ", "おろか", "おろそか", "とおす", "とおる", "まばら" ] },
	{"question":"喪", "answers":[ "ソウ", "も", "うしなう", "ほろびる", "ほろぼす" ] },
	{"question":"堕", "answers":[ "ダ", "キ", "おちる", "おとす", "おろす", "こぼつ" ] },
	{"question":"惰", "answers":[ "ダ", "タ", "おこたる" ] },
	{"question":"棚", "answers":[ "たな", "ホウ" ] },
	{"question":"塚", "answers":[ "つか", "チョウ" ] },
	{"question":"搭", "answers":[ "トウ", "のせる", "のる" ] },
	{"question":"筒", "answers":[ "トウ", "つつ" ] },
	{"question":"棟", "answers":[ "トウ", "むね", "むな", "かしら" ] },
	{"question":"廃", "answers":[ "ハイ", "すたる", "すたれる", "やめる" ] },
	{"question":"媒", "answers":[ "バイ", "なかだち" ] },
	{"question":"扉", "answers":[ "とびら", "ヒ" ] },
	{"question":"雰", "answers":[ "フン", "きり" ] },
	{"question":"塀", "answers":[ "ヘイ" ] },
	{"question":"遍", "answers":[ "ヘン", "あまねく" ] },
	{"question":"愉", "answers":[ "ユ", "たのしい", "たのしむ" ] },
	{"question":"裕", "answers":[ "ユウ", "ひろい", "ゆたか" ] },
	{"question":"猶", "answers":[ "ユウ", "なお" ] },
	{"question":"痢", "answers":[ "リ" ] },
	{"question":"硫", "answers":[ "リュウ", "ル" ] },
	{"question":"塁", "answers":[ "ルイ", "かさねる", "とりで" ] },
	{"question":"嵐", "answers":[ "あらし", "ラン" ] },
	{"question":"椅", "answers":[ "イ" ] },
	{"question":"媛", "answers":[ "エン", "ひめ" ] },
	{"question":"葛", "answers":[ "カツ", "くず", "かずら", "かたびら", "つづら" ] },
	{"question":"喉", "answers":[ "コウ", "のど" ] },
	{"question":"須", "answers":[ "ス", "シュ", "しばらく", "すべからく", "まつ", "もちいる", "もとめる" ] },
	{"question":"痩", "answers":[ "やせる", "ソウ", "シュウ", "こける", "ほそい" ] },
	{"question":"貼", "answers":[ "チョウ", "はる", "テン", "つける" ] },
	{"question":"椎", "answers":[ "ツイ", "スイ", "うつ", "しい", "せぼね", "つち" ] },
	{"question":"斑", "answers":[ "ハン", "ふ", "ぶち", "まだら" ] },
	{"question":"喩", "answers":[ "ユ", "さとす", "たとえる", "よろこぶ" ] },
	{"question":"湧", "answers":[ "ユウ", "わく", "ヨウ" ] },
	{"question":"貿", "answers":[ "ボウ", "あきなう" ] },
	{"question":"遠", "answers":[ "エン", "とおい", "オン", "おち" ] },
	{"question":"園", "answers":[ "エン", "その", "オン", "にわ" ] },
	{"question":"楽", "answers":[ "ガク", "ラク", "たのしい", "たのしむ", "ギョウ", "ゴウ", "かなでる", "このむ" ] },
	{"question":"新", "answers":[ "シン", "あたらしい", "あらた", "にい", "さら" ] },
	{"question":"数", "answers":[ "スウ", "かず", "かぞえる", "ス", "サク", "シュ", "ソク", "しばしば" ] },
	{"question":"電", "answers":[ "デン", "テン", "いなずま" ] },
	{"question":"話", "answers":[ "ワ", "はなし", "はなす" ] },
	{"question":"暗", "answers":[ "アン", "くらい", "そらんじる", "やみ" ] },
	{"question":"意", "answers":[ "イ", "おもう", "こころ" ] },
	{"question":"感", "answers":[ "カン" ] },
	{"question":"漢", "answers":[ "カン", "おとこ", "から" ] },
	{"question":"業", "answers":[ "ギョウ", "わざ", "ゴウ" ] },
	{"question":"詩", "answers":[ "シ", "うた" ] },
	{"question":"想", "answers":[ "ソウ", "ソ", "おもう" ] },
	{"question":"鉄", "answers":[ "テツ", "かね", "くろがね" ] },
	{"question":"農", "answers":[ "ノウ", "ドウ", "たがやす" ] },
	{"question":"福", "answers":[ "フク", "さいわい" ] },
	{"question":"路", "answers":[ "ロ", "じ", "くるま", "みち" ] },
	{"question":"愛", "answers":[ "アイ", "いとしい", "うい", "おしむ", "かなしい", "まな", "めでる" ] },
	{"question":"塩", "answers":[ "エン", "しお", "アン" ] },
	{"question":"試", "answers":[ "シ", "こころみる", "ためす" ] },
	{"question":"辞", "answers":[ "ジ", "やめる", "ことば", "ことわる" ] },
	{"question":"照", "answers":[ "ショウ", "てらす", "てる", "てれる" ] },
	{"question":"節", "answers":[ "セツ", "ふし", "セチ", "ノット", "みさお" ] },
	{"question":"戦", "answers":[ "セン", "たたかう", "いくさ", "おののく", "そよぐ" ] },
	{"question":"続", "answers":[ "ゾク", "つづく", "つづける", "ショク", "つぐ" ] },
	{"question":"置", "answers":[ "チ", "おく" ] },
	{"question":"腸", "answers":[ "チョウ", "はらわた", "わた" ] },
	{"question":"働", "answers":[ "ドウ", "はたらく" ] },
	{"question":"解", "answers":[ "カイ", "とかす", "とく", "とける", "ゲ", "さとる", "ほぐれる", "ほつれる", "ほどく", "ほどける", "わかる" ] },
	{"question":"幹", "answers":[ "カン", "みき", "から", "わざ" ] },
	{"question":"義", "answers":[ "ギ", "よい" ] },
	{"question":"禁", "answers":[ "キン", "いさめる", "いむ", "とどめる" ] },
	{"question":"群", "answers":[ "グン", "むら", "むれ", "むれる" ] },
	{"question":"鉱", "answers":[ "コウ", "あらがね" ] },
	{"question":"罪", "answers":[ "ザイ", "つみ" ] },
	{"question":"資", "answers":[ "シ", "たから", "たすける", "たち", "もと" ] },
	{"question":"飼", "answers":[ "シ", "かう", "やしなう" ] },
	{"question":"準", "answers":[ "ジュン", "シュン", "セツ", "なぞらえる", "みずもり" ] },
	{"question":"勢", "answers":[ "セイ", "いきおい", "セ" ] },
	{"question":"損", "answers":[ "ソン", "そこなう", "そこねる", "へる" ] },
	{"question":"墓", "answers":[ "ボ", "はか" ] },
	{"question":"豊", "answers":[ "ホウ", "ゆたか", "とよ" ] },
	{"question":"夢", "answers":[ "ム", "ゆめ", "ボウ" ] },
	{"question":"預", "answers":[ "ヨ", "あずかる", "あずける", "あらかじめ" ] },
	{"question":"絹", "answers":[ "きぬ", "ケン" ] },
	{"question":"源", "answers":[ "ゲン", "みなもと" ] },
	{"question":"署", "answers":[ "ショ", "しるす", "やくわり" ] },
	{"question":"傷", "answers":[ "ショウ", "きず", "いたむ", "いためる", "そこなう" ] },
	{"question":"蒸", "answers":[ "ジョウ", "むす", "むらす", "むれる", "おおい", "ふかす", "ふける" ] },
	{"question":"誠", "answers":[ "セイ", "まこと", "ジョウ" ] },
	{"question":"聖", "answers":[ "セイ", "ショウ", "ひじり" ] },
	{"question":"暖", "answers":[ "ダン", "あたたか", "あたたかい", "あたたまる", "あたためる", "ノン" ] },
	{"question":"賃", "answers":[ "チン", "ジン", "やとう" ] },
	{"question":"腹", "answers":[ "フク", "はら", "こころ" ] },
	{"question":"幕", "answers":[ "バク", "マク" ] },
	{"question":"盟", "answers":[ "メイ", "ちかう" ] },
	{"question":"裏", "answers":[ "うら", "リ", "うち" ] },
	{"question":"違", "answers":[ "イ", "ちがう", "ちがえる", "かい", "さる", "たがう", "たがえる", "よこしま" ] },
	{"question":"煙", "answers":[ "エン", "けむい", "けむり", "けむる", "けぶる", "けむ" ] },
	{"question":"鉛", "answers":[ "エン", "なまり", "おしろい" ] },
	{"question":"暇", "answers":[ "カ", "ひま", "いとま" ] },
	{"question":"雅", "answers":[ "ガ", "ア", "つね", "みやび", "みやびやか" ] },
	{"question":"較", "answers":[ "カク", "コウ", "くらべる" ] },
	{"question":"勧", "answers":[ "カン", "すすめる", "ケン" ] },
	{"question":"詰", "answers":[ "つまる", "つむ", "つめる", "キツ", "なじる" ] },
	{"question":"傾", "answers":[ "ケイ", "かたむく", "かたむける", "かしぐ", "かたげる", "くつがえる" ] },
	{"question":"遣", "answers":[ "ケン", "つかう", "つかわす", "やる" ] },
	{"question":"誇", "answers":[ "コ", "ほこる" ] },
	{"question":"鼓", "answers":[ "コ", "つづみ" ] },
	{"question":"継", "answers":[ "ケイ", "つぐ", "まま" ] },
	{"question":"歳", "answers":[ "サイ", "セイ", "とし", "とせ", "よわい" ] },
	{"question":"載", "answers":[ "サイ", "のせる", "のる", "しるす", "とし" ] },
	{"question":"詳", "answers":[ "ショウ", "くわしい", "ヨウ", "つまびらか" ] },
	{"question":"飾", "answers":[ "ショク", "かざる", "かざり" ] },
	{"question":"触", "answers":[ "ショク", "さわる", "ふれる", "ソク" ] },
	{"question":"慎", "answers":[ "シン", "つつしむ", "つつましい", "つつましやか" ] },
	{"question":"寝", "answers":[ "シン", "ねかす", "ねる", "みたまや", "みにくい", "やめる" ] },
	{"question":"跡", "answers":[ "セキ", "あと", "シャク", "あとかた" ] },
	{"question":"僧", "answers":[ "ソウ" ] },
	{"question":"嘆", "answers":[ "タン", "なげかわしい", "なげく" ] },
	{"question":"蓄", "answers":[ "チク", "たくわえる" ] },
	{"question":"跳", "answers":[ "チョウ", "とぶ", "はねる", "トウ", "おどる" ] },
	{"question":"殿", "answers":[ "テン", "デン", "との", "どの", "しんがり" ] },
	{"question":"搬", "answers":[ "ハン", "はこぶ" ] },
	{"question":"微", "answers":[ "ビ", "ミ", "かすか" ] },
	{"question":"誉", "answers":[ "ヨ", "ほまれ", "ほめる" ] },
	{"question":"腰", "answers":[ "こし", "ヨウ" ] },
	{"question":"溶", "answers":[ "ヨウ", "とかす", "とく", "とける" ] },
	{"question":"雷", "answers":[ "ライ", "かみなり", "いかずち" ] },
	{"question":"嫁", "answers":[ "とつぐ", "よめ", "カ" ] },
	{"question":"塊", "answers":[ "カイ", "かたまり", "つちくれ" ] },
	{"question":"慨", "answers":[ "ガイ", "カイ", "いきどおる", "なげく" ] },
	{"question":"該", "answers":[ "ガイ", "カイ", "かねる", "そなわる", "その" ] },
	{"question":"隔", "answers":[ "カク", "へだたる", "へだてる" ] },
	{"question":"滑", "answers":[ "カツ", "コツ", "すべる", "なめらか", "ぬめる" ] },
	{"question":"棄", "answers":[ "キ", "すてる" ] },
	{"question":"愚", "answers":[ "グ", "おろか" ] },
	{"question":"携", "answers":[ "ケイ", "たずさえる", "たずさわる", "はなれる" ] },
	{"question":"催", "answers":[ "サイ", "もよおす", "うながす", "もよい" ] },
	{"question":"債", "answers":[ "サイ", "かし", "かり" ] },
	{"question":"搾", "answers":[ "しぼる", "サク" ] },
	{"question":"慈", "answers":[ "ジ", "いつくしむ" ] },
	{"question":"摂", "answers":[ "セツ", "ショウ", "かねる", "かわる", "とる" ] },
	{"question":"賊", "answers":[ "ゾク", "そこなう", "わるもの" ] },
	{"question":"滞", "answers":[ "タイ", "とどこおる" ] },
	{"question":"滝", "answers":[ "たき", "ロウ" ] },
	{"question":"稚", "answers":[ "チ", "いとけない", "わかい" ] },
	{"question":"塗", "answers":[ "ト", "ぬる", "どろ", "まぶす", "まみれる", "みち" ] },
	{"question":"飽", "answers":[ "ホウ", "あかす", "あきる" ] },
	{"question":"滅", "answers":[ "メツ", "ほろびる", "ほろぼす", "ベツ" ] },
	{"question":"裸", "answers":[ "ラ", "はだか" ] },
	{"question":"零", "answers":[ "レイ", "あまり", "おちる", "こぼれる", "ゼロ", "ふる" ] },
	{"question":"廉", "answers":[ "レン", "いさぎよい", "かど", "やすい" ] },
	{"question":"楼", "answers":[ "ロウ", "たかどの", "やぐら" ] },
	{"question":"猿", "answers":[ "エン", "さる", "ましら" ] },
	{"question":"虞", "answers":[ "おそれ", "グ" ] },
	{"question":"禍", "answers":[ "カ", "まが", "わざわい" ] },
	{"question":"靴", "answers":[ "くつ", "カ" ] },
	{"question":"褐", "answers":[ "カツ", "ぬのこ" ] },
	{"question":"寛", "answers":[ "カン", "くつろぐ", "ひろい", "ゆるやか" ] },
	{"question":"頑", "answers":[ "ガン", "かたくな" ] },
	{"question":"傑", "answers":[ "ケツ", "すぐれる" ] },
	{"question":"嫌", "answers":[ "ケン", "ゲン", "いや", "きらう", "うたがう" ] },
	{"question":"献", "answers":[ "ケン", "コン", "ささげる", "たてまつる", "まつる" ] },
	{"question":"碁", "answers":[ "ゴ", "キ" ] },
	{"question":"溝", "answers":[ "コウ", "みぞ", "どぶ" ] },
	{"question":"嗣", "answers":[ "シ", "つぐ" ] },
	{"question":"酬", "answers":[ "シュウ", "むくいる" ] },
	{"question":"愁", "answers":[ "シュウ", "うれい", "うれえる" ] },
	{"question":"奨", "answers":[ "ショウ", "ソウ", "すすめる" ] },
	{"question":"睡", "answers":[ "スイ", "ねむる" ] },
	{"question":"践", "answers":[ "セン", "ふむ" ] },
	{"question":"禅", "answers":[ "ゼン", "セン", "ゆずる" ] },
	{"question":"塑", "answers":[ "ソ", "でく" ] },
	{"question":"痴", "answers":[ "チ", "おこ", "おろか", "しれる" ] },
	{"question":"艇", "answers":[ "テイ", "こぶね" ] },
	{"question":"督", "answers":[ "トク", "うながす", "かしら", "ただす", "ひきいる", "みる" ] },
	{"question":"漠", "answers":[ "バク", "マク", "すなはら", "ひろい" ] },
	{"question":"鉢", "answers":[ "ハチ", "ハツ" ] },
	{"question":"煩", "answers":[ "ハン", "わずらう", "わずらわす", "ボン", "うるさい" ] },
	{"question":"頒", "answers":[ "ハン", "フン", "しく", "まだら", "わける" ] },
	{"question":"酪", "answers":[ "ラク", "ちちしる" ] },
	{"question":"虜", "answers":[ "リョ", "ロ", "えびす", "しもべ", "とりこ" ] },
	{"question":"鈴", "answers":[ "リン", "レイ", "すず" ] },
	{"question":"賄", "answers":[ "ワイ", "まかなう", "カイ", "まいなう" ] },
	{"question":"彙", "answers":[ "イ", "あつめる", "たぐい", "はりねずみ" ] },
	{"question":"楷", "answers":[ "カイ", "のっとる", "のり" ] },
	{"question":"蓋", "answers":[ "ガイ", "ふた", "コウ", "おおい", "おおう", "かさ", "けだし" ] },
	{"question":"毀", "answers":[ "キ", "こぼつ", "こわす", "そしる", "やせる", "やぶる", "やぶれる" ] },
	{"question":"嗅", "answers":[ "キュウ", "かぐ" ] },
	{"question":"僅", "answers":[ "キン", "わずか", "わずかに" ] },
	{"question":"窟", "answers":[ "クツ", "いわや", "ほらあな" ] },
	{"question":"詣", "answers":[ "もうでる", "ケイ", "いたる", "まいる" ] },
	{"question":"隙", "answers":[ "すき", "ゲキ", "ケキ", "ひま" ] },
	{"question":"傲", "answers":[ "ゴウ", "あそぶ", "あなどる", "おごる" ] },
	{"question":"塞", "answers":[ "サイ", "ソク", "ふさがる", "ふさぐ", "せく", "とりで", "みちる" ] },
	{"question":"嫉", "answers":[ "シツ", "そねむ", "にくむ", "ねたむ" ] },
	{"question":"腫", "answers":[ "シュ", "はらす", "はれる", "ショウ", "はれもの" ] },
	{"question":"腎", "answers":[ "ジン", "シン" ] },
	{"question":"裾", "answers":[ "すそ", "キョ" ] },
	{"question":"煎", "answers":[ "セン", "いる", "にる" ] },
	{"question":"羨", "answers":[ "うらやましい", "うらやむ", "セン", "エン", "ゼン", "あまる", "はかみち" ] },
	{"question":"腺", "answers":[ "セン", "すじ" ] },
	{"question":"詮", "answers":[ "セン", "あきらか", "えらぶ", "しらべる", "そなわる" ] },
	{"question":"溺", "answers":[ "デキ", "おぼれる", "ジョウ", "ニョウ", "いばり", "ゆばり" ] },
	{"question":"頓", "answers":[ "トン", "トツ", "くるしむ", "つかれる", "つまずく", "とどまる", "とみに", "ぬかずく", "ひたぶる" ] },
	{"question":"蜂", "answers":[ "ホウ", "はち", "むらがる" ] },
	{"question":"睦", "answers":[ "ボク", "モク", "むつぶ", "むつまじい", "むつむ" ] },
	{"question":"慄", "answers":[ "リツ", "おそれる", "おののく" ] },
	{"question":"賂", "answers":[ "ロ", "まいない", "まいなう" ] },
	{"question":"塡", "answers":[ "テン", "チン", "うずまる", "うずめる", "はまる", "はめる", "ふさがる", "ふさぐ" ] },
	{"question":"歌", "answers":[ "カ", "うた", "うたう" ] },
	{"question":"語", "answers":[ "ゴ", "かたらう", "かたる", "ギョ", "ことば", "つげる" ] },
	{"question":"算", "answers":[ "サン", "かず", "かぞえる" ] },
	{"question":"読", "answers":[ "トウ", "トク", "ドク", "よむ" ] },
	{"question":"聞", "answers":[ "ブン", "きく", "きこえる", "モン" ] },
	{"question":"鳴", "answers":[ "メイ", "なく", "ならす", "なる", "ミョウ" ] },
	{"question":"駅", "answers":[ "エキ", "うまや" ] },
	{"question":"銀", "answers":[ "ギン", "しろがね" ] },
	{"question":"鼻", "answers":[ "はな", "ビ", "はじめ" ] },
	{"question":"様", "answers":[ "ヨウ", "さま" ] },
	{"question":"緑", "answers":[ "リョク", "みどり", "ロク" ] },
	{"question":"練", "answers":[ "レン", "ねる", "ねりぎぬ" ] },
	{"question":"関", "answers":[ "カン", "かかわる", "せき", "からくり", "かんぬき" ] },
	{"question":"管", "answers":[ "カン", "くだ", "つかさどる", "ふえ" ] },
	{"question":"旗", "answers":[ "キ", "はた" ] },
	{"question":"察", "answers":[ "サツ", "あきらか", "しる", "みる" ] },
	{"question":"種", "answers":[ "シュ", "たね", "ショウ", "うえる", "くさ" ] },
	{"question":"静", "answers":[ "セイ", "しず", "しずか", "しずまる", "しずめる", "ジョウ" ] },
	{"question":"説", "answers":[ "セツ", "とく", "ゼイ", "エツ", "よろこぶ" ] },
	{"question":"漁", "answers":[ "ギョ", "リョウ", "あさる", "いさり", "すなどる" ] },
	{"question":"歴", "answers":[ "レキ", "リャク", "へる" ] },
	{"question":"演", "answers":[ "エン", "おこなう", "のべる" ] },
	{"question":"慣", "answers":[ "カン", "ならす", "なれる", "ならわし" ] },
	{"question":"境", "answers":[ "キョウ", "さかい", "ケイ" ] },
	{"question":"構", "answers":[ "コウ", "かまう", "かまえる" ] },
	{"question":"際", "answers":[ "サイ", "きわ", "あい", "まじわる" ] },
	{"question":"雑", "answers":[ "ザツ", "ゾウ", "まじる", "まぜる" ] },
	{"question":"酸", "answers":[ "サン", "すい", "す", "つらい" ] },
	{"question":"製", "answers":[ "セイ", "つくる" ] },
	{"question":"精", "answers":[ "セイ", "ショウ", "くわしい", "しらげる", "もののけ" ] },
	{"question":"銭", "answers":[ "セン", "ぜに", "ゼン", "すき" ] },
	{"question":"総", "answers":[ "ソウ", "すべて", "すべる", "ふさ" ] },
	{"question":"増", "answers":[ "ゾウ", "ふえる", "ふやす", "ます", "ソウ" ] },
	{"question":"像", "answers":[ "ゾウ", "ショウ", "かたち", "かたどる" ] },
	{"question":"態", "answers":[ "タイ", "テイ", "さま", "わざと" ] },
	{"question":"適", "answers":[ "テキ", "セキ", "タク", "かなう", "たまたま", "ゆく" ] },
	{"question":"銅", "answers":[ "ドウ", "あかがね" ] },
	{"question":"徳", "answers":[ "トク" ] },
	{"question":"複", "answers":[ "フク", "かさねる" ] },
	{"question":"綿", "answers":[ "メン", "わた", "ベン", "つらなる" ] },
	{"question":"領", "answers":[ "リョウ", "うなじ", "えり", "うける", "おさめる", "かしら", "かなめ" ] },
	{"question":"閣", "answers":[ "カク", "たかどの", "たな" ] },
	{"question":"疑", "answers":[ "ギ", "うたがう", "うたぐる" ] },
	{"question":"誤", "answers":[ "ゴ", "あやまる", "まどわす" ] },
	{"question":"穀", "answers":[ "コク" ] },
	{"question":"誌", "answers":[ "シ", "しるす" ] },
	{"question":"磁", "answers":[ "ジ", "シ", "やきもの" ] },
	{"question":"障", "answers":[ "ショウ", "さわる", "ふせぐ", "へだてる" ] },
	{"question":"層", "answers":[ "ソウ", "かさなる" ] },
	{"question":"認", "answers":[ "みとめる", "ニン", "ジン", "したためる" ] },
	{"question":"暮", "answers":[ "くらす", "くれる", "ボ" ] },
	{"question":"模", "answers":[ "ボ", "モ", "かた", "のっとる" ] },
	{"question":"維", "answers":[ "イ", "これ", "つなぐ" ] },
	{"question":"隠", "answers":[ "イン", "かくす", "かくれる", "オン" ] },
	{"question":"箇", "answers":[ "カ", "コ" ] },
	{"question":"駆", "answers":[ "ク", "かける", "かる", "おう" ] },
	{"question":"豪", "answers":[ "ゴウ", "コウ", "えらい", "つよい" ] },
	{"question":"雌", "answers":[ "シ", "め", "めす", "めん" ] },
	{"question":"需", "answers":[ "ジュ", "もとめる" ] },
	{"question":"端", "answers":[ "タン", "はし", "はた", "は", "ただしい", "はした", "はじめ", "はな" ] },
	{"question":"徴", "answers":[ "チョウ", "チ", "しるし", "めす" ] },
	{"question":"摘", "answers":[ "テキ", "つむ", "つまむ" ] },
	{"question":"滴", "answers":[ "テキ", "しずく", "したたる", "たれる" ] },
	{"question":"稲", "answers":[ "トウ", "いな", "いね" ] },
	{"question":"髪", "answers":[ "ハツ", "かみ", "ホツ" ] },
	{"question":"罰", "answers":[ "バチ", "バツ", "ハツ" ] },
	{"question":"腐", "answers":[ "フ", "くさらす", "くさる", "くされる", "くさす" ] },
	{"question":"漫", "answers":[ "マン", "バン", "そぞろに", "みだりに" ] },
	{"question":"慢", "answers":[ "マン", "バン", "あなどる", "おこたる", "おごる" ] },
	{"question":"網", "answers":[ "モウ", "あみ", "ボウ" ] },
	{"question":"踊", "answers":[ "ヨウ", "おどり", "おどる" ] },
	{"question":"暦", "answers":[ "レキ", "こよみ", "リャク" ] },
	{"question":"概", "answers":[ "ガイ", "カイ", "おおむね" ] },
	{"question":"綱", "answers":[ "コウ", "つな" ] },
	{"question":"酵", "answers":[ "コウ", "こうじ", "もと" ] },
	{"question":"獄", "answers":[ "ゴク", "うったえる", "ひとや" ] },
	{"question":"魂", "answers":[ "コン", "たましい", "たま" ] },
	{"question":"遭", "answers":[ "ソウ", "あう" ] },
	{"question":"憎", "answers":[ "ゾウ", "にくい", "にくしみ", "にくむ", "にくらしい", "ソウ" ] },
	{"question":"奪", "answers":[ "ダツ", "うばう", "タツ" ] },
	{"question":"碑", "answers":[ "ヒ", "いしぶみ" ] },
	{"question":"漂", "answers":[ "ヒョウ", "ただよう", "さらす" ] },
	{"question":"慕", "answers":[ "ボ", "したう", "しのぶ" ] },
	{"question":"墨", "answers":[ "ボク", "すみ", "モク" ] },
	{"question":"膜", "answers":[ "マク", "バク", "ボ", "モ" ] },
	{"question":"誘", "answers":[ "ユウ", "さそう", "いざなう", "おびく" ] },
	{"question":"漏", "answers":[ "ロウ", "もらす", "もる", "もれる" ] },
	{"question":"寡", "answers":[ "カ", "すくない", "やもめ" ] },
	{"question":"酷", "answers":[ "コク", "きびしい", "はなはだしい", "ひどい", "むごい" ] },
	{"question":"漆", "answers":[ "シツ", "うるし", "シチ" ] },
	{"question":"遮", "answers":[ "シャ", "さえぎる" ] },
	{"question":"銃", "answers":[ "ジュウ", "つつ" ] },
	{"question":"塾", "answers":[ "ジュク" ] },
	{"question":"緒", "answers":[ "ショ", "チョ", "お", "いとぐち" ] },
	{"question":"彰", "answers":[ "ショウ", "あきらか", "あらわす", "あらわれる" ] },
	{"question":"誓", "answers":[ "セイ", "ちかう", "ゼイ" ] },
	{"question":"漸", "answers":[ "ゼン", "ザン", "セン", "すすむ", "やや", "ようやく" ] },
	{"question":"駄", "answers":[ "ダ", "タ", "のせる" ] },
	{"question":"嫡", "answers":[ "チャク", "テキ", "よつぎ" ] },
	{"question":"漬", "answers":[ "つかる", "つける", "シ" ] },
	{"question":"寧", "answers":[ "ネイ", "デイ", "ニョウ", "いずくんぞ", "なんぞ", "ねんごろ", "むしろ", "やすい" ] },
	{"question":"閥", "answers":[ "バツ", "ハツ", "いえがら", "いさお" ] },
	{"question":"僕", "answers":[ "ボク", "ホク", "しもべ", "やつがれ" ] },
	{"question":"銘", "answers":[ "メイ", "ミョウ", "しるす" ] },
	{"question":"僚", "answers":[ "リョウ", "つかさ", "とも" ] },
	{"question":"熊", "answers":[ "くま", "ユウ" ] },
	{"question":"箋", "answers":[ "セン", "かきもの", "てがみ", "ときあかし", "なふだ", "はりふだ", "ふだ" ] },
	{"question":"遡", "answers":[ "さかのぼる", "ソ", "むかう" ] },
	{"question":"遜", "answers":[ "ソン", "のがれる", "へりくだる", "ゆずる" ] },
	{"question":"綻", "answers":[ "タン", "ほころびる", "ほころぶ" ] },
	{"question":"蔑", "answers":[ "ベツ", "さげすむ", "くらい", "ないがしろ", "なみする" ] },
	{"question":"貌", "answers":[ "ボウ", "バク", "かお", "かたち" ] },
	{"question":"蜜", "answers":[ "ミツ", "ビツ" ] },
	{"question":"瘍", "answers":[ "ヨウ", "かさ", "できもの" ] },
	{"question":"辣", "answers":[ "ラツ", "からい", "きびしい", "むごい" ] },
	{"question":"瑠", "answers":[ "ル" ] },
	{"question":"線", "answers":[ "セン", "いと", "すじ" ] },
	{"question":"横", "answers":[ "オウ", "よこ", "コウ", "よこたわる" ] },
	{"question":"談", "answers":[ "ダン", "タン", "かたる" ] },
	{"question":"調", "answers":[ "チョウ", "しらべる", "ととのう", "ととのえる", "あざける", "みつぎ", "やわらぐ" ] },
	{"question":"箱", "answers":[ "はこ", "ショウ", "ソウ" ] },
	{"question":"億", "answers":[ "オク", "おしはかる" ] },
	{"question":"課", "answers":[ "カ", "こころみる", "はかる", "わりあてる" ] },
	{"question":"器", "answers":[ "キ", "うつわ" ] },
	{"question":"賞", "answers":[ "ショウ", "ほめる", "めでる" ] },
	{"question":"選", "answers":[ "セン", "えらぶ", "える", "すぐる", "よる" ] },
	{"question":"熱", "answers":[ "ネツ", "あつい", "いきる", "ほてる", "ほとぼり" ] },
	{"question":"標", "answers":[ "ヒョウ", "こずえ", "しめ", "しるし", "しるす", "しるべ" ] },
	{"question":"養", "answers":[ "ヨウ", "やしなう", "やしない" ] },
	{"question":"輪", "answers":[ "リン", "わ" ] },
	{"question":"確", "answers":[ "カク", "たしか", "たしかめる", "かたい", "しかと", "しっかり" ] },
	{"question":"潔", "answers":[ "ケツ", "いさぎよい", "きよい" ] },
	{"question":"賛", "answers":[ "サン", "たすける", "たたえる", "ほめる" ] },
	{"question":"質", "answers":[ "シツ", "シチ", "チ", "シ", "ただす", "たち", "もと" ] },
	{"question":"敵", "answers":[ "テキ", "かたき", "あだ", "かなう" ] },
	{"question":"導", "answers":[ "ドウ", "みちびく", "しるべ" ] },
	{"question":"編", "answers":[ "ヘン", "あむ", "とじいと", "ふみ" ] },
	{"question":"暴", "answers":[ "ボウ", "あばれる", "バク", "あばく", "あらい", "あらわす", "さらす", "にわか" ] },
	{"question":"遺", "answers":[ "イ", "ユイ", "すてる", "のこす", "のこる", "わすれる" ] },
	{"question":"劇", "answers":[ "ゲキ", "はげしい" ] },
	{"question":"権", "answers":[ "ケン", "ゴン", "いきおい", "おもり", "かり", "はかる" ] },
	{"question":"熟", "answers":[ "ジュク", "うれる", "うむ", "こなす", "こなれる", "つくづく", "つらつら", "なれる", "にえる", "にる" ] },
	{"question":"諸", "answers":[ "ショ", "もろ", "もろもろ" ] },
	{"question":"蔵", "answers":[ "ゾウ", "くら", "ソウ", "おさめる", "かくれる" ] },
	{"question":"誕", "answers":[ "タン", "いつわる", "うまれる", "ほしいまま" ] },
	{"question":"潮", "answers":[ "チョウ", "しお", "うしお" ] },
	{"question":"論", "answers":[ "ロン", "あげつらう", "とく" ] },
	{"question":"鋭", "answers":[ "エイ", "するどい", "はやい" ] },
	{"question":"影", "answers":[ "エイ", "かげ", "ヨウ" ] },
	{"question":"縁", "answers":[ "エン", "ふち", "えにし", "へり", "ゆかり", "よすが", "よる" ] },
	{"question":"監", "answers":[ "カン", "ケン", "かんがみる", "しらべる", "みる" ] },
	{"question":"歓", "answers":[ "カン", "よろこぶ" ] },
	{"question":"輝", "answers":[ "キ", "かがやく", "てる" ] },
	{"question":"儀", "answers":[ "ギ", "のり", "よい" ] },
	{"question":"戯", "answers":[ "ギ", "たわむれる", "ゲ", "ざれる", "たわける" ] },
	{"question":"撃", "answers":[ "ゲキ", "うつ", "ケキ" ] },
	{"question":"稿", "answers":[ "コウ", "したがき", "わら" ] },
	{"question":"趣", "answers":[ "シュ", "おもむき", "ソク", "うながす", "おもむく" ] },
	{"question":"震", "answers":[ "シン", "ふるう", "ふるえる" ] },
	{"question":"澄", "answers":[ "すます", "すむ", "チョウ" ] },
	{"question":"踏", "answers":[ "トウ", "ふまえる", "ふむ" ] },
	{"question":"輩", "answers":[ "ハイ", "ともがら", "やから" ] },
	{"question":"範", "answers":[ "ハン", "いがた", "のり" ] },
	{"question":"盤", "answers":[ "バン", "ハン", "おおざら", "まがる", "めぐる", "わだかまる" ] },
	{"question":"膚", "answers":[ "フ", "はだ", "はだえ" ] },
	{"question":"敷", "answers":[ "しく", "フ" ] },
	{"question":"賦", "answers":[ "フ", "みつぎ", "わかつ" ] },
	{"question":"舞", "answers":[ "ブ", "まい", "まう", "ム", "もてあそぶ" ] },
	{"question":"噴", "answers":[ "フン", "ふく", "ホン", "はく" ] },
	{"question":"舗", "answers":[ "ホ", "フ", "しく", "みせ" ] },
	{"question":"黙", "answers":[ "モク", "だまる", "ボク", "だんまり", "もだす" ] },
	{"question":"慮", "answers":[ "リョ", "おもんぱかる" ] },
	{"question":"慰", "answers":[ "イ", "なぐさむ", "なぐさめる" ] },
	{"question":"閲", "answers":[ "エツ", "けみする", "へる" ] },
	{"question":"餓", "answers":[ "ガ", "うえ", "うえる" ] },
	{"question":"緩", "answers":[ "カン", "ゆるい", "ゆるむ", "ゆるめる", "ゆるやか", "ぬるい" ] },
	{"question":"緊", "answers":[ "キン", "かたい", "きびしい", "しめる", "ちぢむ" ] },
	{"question":"撮", "answers":[ "サツ", "とる", "つまむ" ] },
	{"question":"暫", "answers":[ "ザン", "しばし", "しばらく" ] },
	{"question":"潤", "answers":[ "ジュン", "うるおう", "うるおす", "うるむ", "ほとびる" ] },
	{"question":"遵", "answers":[ "ジュン", "シュン", "したがう" ] },
	{"question":"衝", "answers":[ "ショウ", "つく" ] },
	{"question":"嘱", "answers":[ "ショク", "たのむ" ] },
	{"question":"審", "answers":[ "シン", "つまびらか" ] },
	{"question":"穂", "answers":[ "ほ", "スイ" ] },
	{"question":"請", "answers":[ "セイ", "うける", "シン", "こう", "ショウ" ] },
	{"question":"潜", "answers":[ "セン", "ひそむ", "もぐる", "くぐる" ] },
	{"question":"諾", "answers":[ "ダク", "うべなう" ] },
	{"question":"駐", "answers":[ "チュウ", "チュ", "とどまる" ] },
	{"question":"鋳", "answers":[ "チュウ", "いる", "シュ" ] },
	{"question":"墜", "answers":[ "ツイ", "おちる", "おとす" ] },
	{"question":"締", "answers":[ "テイ", "しまる", "しめる", "むすぶ" ] },
	{"question":"墳", "answers":[ "フン", "はか" ] },
	{"question":"魅", "answers":[ "ミ", "ビ", "すだま", "もののけ" ] },
	{"question":"憂", "answers":[ "ユウ", "うれい", "うれえる", "うい" ] },
	{"question":"霊", "answers":[ "レイ", "リョウ", "たま", "たましい", "よい" ] },
	{"question":"謁", "answers":[ "エツ", "まみえる" ] },
	{"question":"稼", "answers":[ "かせぐ", "カ", "うえる", "みのり" ] },
	{"question":"潟", "answers":[ "かた", "セキ" ] },
	{"question":"窮", "answers":[ "キュウ", "きわまる", "きわめる" ] },
	{"question":"勲", "answers":[ "クン", "いさお", "いさおし" ] },
	{"question":"慶", "answers":[ "ケイ", "キョウ", "よい", "よろこぶ" ] },
	{"question":"賜", "answers":[ "たまわる", "シ", "たまう", "たまもの" ] },
	{"question":"縄", "answers":[ "ジョウ", "なわ", "ただす" ] },
	{"question":"遷", "answers":[ "セン", "うつす", "うつる" ] },
	{"question":"槽", "answers":[ "ソウ", "おけ", "かいばおけ", "ふね" ] },
	{"question":"徹", "answers":[ "テツ", "とおる" ] },
	{"question":"撤", "answers":[ "テツ", "すてる" ] },
	{"question":"賠", "answers":[ "バイ", "つぐなう" ] },
	{"question":"罷", "answers":[ "ヒ", "つかれる", "まかる", "やめる" ] },
	{"question":"賓", "answers":[ "ヒン", "したがう", "まろうど" ] },
	{"question":"憤", "answers":[ "フン", "いきどおる", "むずかる" ] },
	{"question":"幣", "answers":[ "ヘイ", "ぜに", "ぬさ", "みてぐら" ] },
	{"question":"弊", "answers":[ "ヘイ", "ついえる", "つかれる", "やぶれる" ] },
	{"question":"褒", "answers":[ "ほめる", "ホウ" ] },
	{"question":"撲", "answers":[ "ボク", "ホク", "うつ", "なぐる", "はる" ] },
	{"question":"摩", "answers":[ "マ", "こする", "さする", "する" ] },
	{"question":"窯", "answers":[ "かま", "ヨウ" ] },
	{"question":"履", "answers":[ "リ", "はく", "くつ", "ふむ" ] },
	{"question":"寮", "answers":[ "リョウ", "つかさ" ] },
	{"question":"潰", "answers":[ "カイ", "つぶす", "つぶれる", "ついえる", "みだれる" ] },
	{"question":"畿", "answers":[ "キ", "みやこ" ] },
	{"question":"憬", "answers":[ "ケイ", "あこがれる" ] },
	{"question":"稽", "answers":[ "ケイ", "かんがえる", "とどこおる", "とどめる" ] },
	{"question":"駒", "answers":[ "こま", "ク" ] },
	{"question":"摯", "answers":[ "シ", "あらい", "とる", "にえ", "まこと" ] },
	{"question":"餌", "answers":[ "え", "えさ", "ジ", "くう", "たべもの" ] },
	{"question":"憧", "answers":[ "ショウ", "あこがれる", "トウ", "ドウ" ] },
	{"question":"踪", "answers":[ "ソウ", "シュウ", "あと" ] },
	{"question":"誰", "answers":[ "だれ", "スイ", "た", "たれ" ] },
	{"question":"嘲", "answers":[ "チョウ", "あざける", "トウ", "からかう" ] },
	{"question":"罵", "answers":[ "バ", "ののしる" ] },
	{"question":"箸", "answers":[ "はし", "チョ" ] },
	{"question":"膝", "answers":[ "ひざ", "シツ" ] },
	{"question":"蔽", "answers":[ "ヘイ", "おおい", "おおう", "くらい", "さだめる" ] },
	{"question":"餅", "answers":[ "ヘイ", "もち" ] },
	{"question":"璃", "answers":[ "リ" ] },
	{"question":"親", "answers":[ "シン", "おや", "したしい", "したしむ", "みずから" ] },
	{"question":"頭", "answers":[ "ズ", "トウ", "あたま", "かしら", "ト", "ジュウ", "かぶり", "かみ", "こうべ", "ほとり" ] },
	{"question":"館", "answers":[ "カン", "やかた", "たち", "たて" ] },
	{"question":"橋", "answers":[ "キョウ", "はし" ] },
	{"question":"整", "answers":[ "セイ", "ととのう", "ととのえる" ] },
	{"question":"薬", "answers":[ "ヤク", "くすり" ] },
	{"question":"機", "answers":[ "キ", "はた", "おり", "からくり", "きざし", "はずみ" ] },
	{"question":"積", "answers":[ "セキ", "つむ", "つもる", "シ", "シャク", "たくわえる" ] },
	{"question":"録", "answers":[ "ロク", "リョ", "リョク", "しるす" ] },
	{"question":"衛", "answers":[ "エイ", "エ", "まもる" ] },
	{"question":"興", "answers":[ "キョウ", "コウ", "おこす", "おこる" ] },
	{"question":"築", "answers":[ "チク", "きずく", "つく" ] },
	{"question":"燃", "answers":[ "ネン", "もえる", "もす", "もやす", "ゼン" ] },
	{"question":"輸", "answers":[ "ユ", "シュ", "いたす", "うつす", "おくる", "まける" ] },
	{"question":"激", "answers":[ "ゲキ", "はげしい", "はげます" ] },
	{"question":"憲", "answers":[ "ケン", "のっとる", "のり" ] },
	{"question":"鋼", "answers":[ "コウ", "はがね" ] },
	{"question":"樹", "answers":[ "ジュ", "うえる", "き", "たてる" ] },
	{"question":"縦", "answers":[ "ジュウ", "たて", "ショウ", "はなつ", "ほしいまま", "ゆるす", "ゆるめる", "よしんば" ] },
	{"question":"操", "answers":[ "ソウ", "あやつる", "みさお", "とる" ] },
	{"question":"糖", "answers":[ "トウ", "あめ" ] },
	{"question":"奮", "answers":[ "フン", "ふるう" ] },
	{"question":"緯", "answers":[ "イ", "ぬき", "よこいと" ] },
	{"question":"憶", "answers":[ "オク", "おぼえる", "おもう" ] },
	{"question":"壊", "answers":[ "カイ", "こわす", "こわれる", "エ", "やぶる", "やぶれる" ] },
	{"question":"獲", "answers":[ "カク", "える" ] },
	{"question":"獣", "answers":[ "ジュウ", "けもの", "けだもの", "しし" ] },
	{"question":"薪", "answers":[ "シン", "たきぎ", "まき" ] },
	{"question":"濁", "answers":[ "ダク", "にごす", "にごる", "ジョク" ] },
	{"question":"曇", "answers":[ "ドン", "くもる", "タン" ] },
	{"question":"濃", "answers":[ "ノウ", "こい", "ジョウ", "こまやか" ] },
	{"question":"薄", "answers":[ "ハク", "うすい", "うすまる", "うすめる", "うすらぐ", "うすれる", "すすき", "せまる" ] },
	{"question":"繁", "answers":[ "ハン", "しげる", "わずらわしい" ] },
	{"question":"避", "answers":[ "ヒ", "さける", "よける" ] },
	{"question":"壁", "answers":[ "ヘキ", "かべ", "がけ" ] },
	{"question":"謡", "answers":[ "ヨウ", "うたい", "うたう" ] },
	{"question":"頼", "answers":[ "ライ", "たのむ", "たのもしい", "たよる", "たより" ] },
	{"question":"隣", "answers":[ "リン", "となり", "となる" ] },
	{"question":"隷", "answers":[ "レイ", "したがう", "しもべ" ] },
	{"question":"穏", "answers":[ "オン", "おだやか", "やすらか" ] },
	{"question":"凝", "answers":[ "ギョウ", "こらす", "こる", "こごる", "しこり" ] },
	{"question":"憩", "answers":[ "ケイ", "いこい", "いこう" ] },
	{"question":"賢", "answers":[ "ケン", "かしこい", "さかしい", "まさる" ] },
	{"question":"墾", "answers":[ "コン", "ひらく" ] },
	{"question":"錯", "answers":[ "サク", "ソ", "あやまる", "おく", "まじる" ] },
	{"question":"諮", "answers":[ "シ", "はかる", "とう" ] },
	{"question":"錠", "answers":[ "ジョウ", "テイ" ] },
	{"question":"嬢", "answers":[ "ジョウ", "むすめ" ] },
	{"question":"壇", "answers":[ "ダン", "タン" ] },
	{"question":"篤", "answers":[ "トク", "あつい" ] },
	{"question":"縛", "answers":[ "バク", "しばる", "ハク", "いましめる" ] },
	{"question":"縫", "answers":[ "ホウ", "ぬう" ] },
	{"question":"謀", "answers":[ "ボウ", "ム", "はかる", "はかりごと" ] },
	{"question":"膨", "answers":[ "ボウ", "ふくらむ", "ふくれる", "ホウ", "ふくよか" ] },
	{"question":"擁", "answers":[ "ヨウ", "いだく", "だく", "まもる" ] },
	{"question":"錬", "answers":[ "レン", "ねる" ] },
	{"question":"懐", "answers":[ "カイ", "なつかしい", "なつかしむ", "なつく", "なつける", "ふところ", "いだく", "おもう" ] },
	{"question":"還", "answers":[ "カン", "ゲン", "かえす", "かえる", "また" ] },
	{"question":"憾", "answers":[ "カン", "うらむ" ] },
	{"question":"薫", "answers":[ "かおる", "クン", "かおりぐさ", "たく" ] },
	{"question":"衡", "answers":[ "コウ", "くびき", "はかり", "はかる" ] },
	{"question":"儒", "answers":[ "ジュ" ] },
	{"question":"壌", "answers":[ "ジョウ", "つち" ] },
	{"question":"薦", "answers":[ "セン", "すすめる", "こも", "しきりに", "しく" ] },
	{"question":"磨", "answers":[ "マ", "みがく", "バ", "する", "とぐ" ] },
	{"question":"諭", "answers":[ "ユ", "さとす" ] },
	{"question":"融", "answers":[ "ユウ", "とおる", "とける" ] },
	{"question":"諧", "answers":[ "カイ", "かなう", "たわむれ", "ととのう", "やわらぐ" ] },
	{"question":"骸", "answers":[ "ガイ", "カイ", "ほね", "むくろ" ] },
	{"question":"錦", "answers":[ "キン", "にしき" ] },
	{"question":"錮", "answers":[ "コ", "かたい", "ながわずらい", "ふさぐ" ] },
	{"question":"醒", "answers":[ "セイ", "さます", "さめる" ] },
	{"question":"膳", "answers":[ "ゼン", "セン", "かしわ", "そなえる" ] },
	{"question":"緻", "answers":[ "チ", "こまかい" ] },
	{"question":"諦", "answers":[ "テイ", "あきらめる", "タイ", "つまびらか", "まこと" ] },
	{"question":"賭", "answers":[ "かける", "ト", "かけ" ] },
	{"question":"麺", "answers":[ "メン", "ベン", "むぎこ" ] },
	{"question":"頰", "answers":[ "ほお", "キョウ" ] },
	{"question":"講", "answers":[ "コウ" ] },
	{"question":"謝", "answers":[ "シャ", "あやまる", "ことわる", "さる" ] },
	{"question":"績", "answers":[ "セキ", "いさお", "うむ", "つむぐ" ] },
	{"question":"厳", "answers":[ "ゲン", "きびしい", "おごそか", "ゴン", "いかつい", "いかめしい" ] },
	{"question":"縮", "answers":[ "シュク", "ちぢまる", "ちぢむ", "ちぢめる", "ちぢらす", "ちぢれる" ] },
	{"question":"優", "answers":[ "ユウ", "すぐれる", "やさしい", "ウ", "まさる", "やわらぐ", "ゆたか", "わざおぎ" ] },
	{"question":"覧", "answers":[ "ラン", "みる" ] },
	{"question":"環", "answers":[ "カン", "たまき", "めぐる", "わ" ] },
	{"question":"鮮", "answers":[ "セン", "あざやか", "あたらしい", "すくない" ] },
	{"question":"燥", "answers":[ "ソウ", "かわく", "はしゃぐ" ] },
	{"question":"翼", "answers":[ "ヨク", "つばさ", "たすける" ] },
	{"question":"療", "answers":[ "リョウ", "いやす" ] },
	{"question":"齢", "answers":[ "レイ", "とし", "よわい" ] },
	{"question":"犠", "answers":[ "ギ", "キ", "いけにえ" ] },
	{"question":"擦", "answers":[ "サツ", "する", "すれる", "かすれる", "こする", "さする", "なする" ] },
	{"question":"鍛", "answers":[ "タン", "きたえる" ] },
	{"question":"聴", "answers":[ "チョウ", "きく", "テイ", "ゆるす" ] },
	{"question":"嚇", "answers":[ "カク", "いかる", "おどかす", "おどす" ] },
	{"question":"轄", "answers":[ "カツ", "くさび", "とりしまる" ] },
	{"question":"擬", "answers":[ "ギ", "なぞらえる", "はかる", "まがい", "もどき" ] },
	{"question":"矯", "answers":[ "キョウ", "ためる", "いつわる" ] },
	{"question":"謹", "answers":[ "キン", "つつしむ" ] },
	{"question":"謙", "answers":[ "ケン", "へりくだる" ] },
	{"question":"購", "answers":[ "コウ", "あがなう" ] },
	{"question":"懇", "answers":[ "コン", "ねんごろ" ] },
	{"question":"爵", "answers":[ "シャク", "さかずき" ] },
	{"question":"醜", "answers":[ "シュウ", "みにくい", "しこ", "たぐい", "にくむ" ] },
	{"question":"償", "answers":[ "ショウ", "つぐなう" ] },
	{"question":"礁", "answers":[ "ショウ", "かくれいわ" ] },
	{"question":"繊", "answers":[ "セン", "チン", "しなやか", "ちいさい", "ほそい" ] },
	{"question":"霜", "answers":[ "しも", "ソウ" ] },
	{"question":"濯", "answers":[ "タク", "あらう", "すすぐ" ] },
	{"question":"謄", "answers":[ "トウ", "うつす" ] },
	{"question":"頻", "answers":[ "ヒン", "ビン", "しきりに", "しきる" ] },
	{"question":"曖", "answers":[ "アイ", "おおう", "かげる", "くらい" ] },
	{"question":"臆", "answers":[ "オク", "おしはかる" ] },
	{"question":"鍵", "answers":[ "ケン", "かぎ" ] },
	{"question":"戴", "answers":[ "タイ", "いただく" ] },
	{"question":"瞳", "answers":[ "ドウ", "ひとみ", "トウ" ] },
	{"question":"謎", "answers":[ "なぞ", "ベイ", "メイ" ] },
	{"question":"鍋", "answers":[ "なべ", "カ" ] },
	{"question":"闇", "answers":[ "やみ", "アン", "くらい" ] },
	{"question":"瞭", "answers":[ "リョウ", "あきらか" ] },
	{"question":"顔", "answers":[ "ガン", "かお", "かんばせ" ] },
	{"question":"曜", "answers":[ "ヨウ", "かがやく" ] },
	{"question":"題", "answers":[ "ダイ", "テイ", "ひたい" ] },
	{"question":"観", "answers":[ "カン", "しめす", "みる", "みせる" ] },
	{"question":"験", "answers":[ "ケン", "ゲン", "あかし", "しるし", "ためす" ] },
	{"question":"類", "answers":[ "ルイ", "たぐい", "たぐい", "たぐえる", "にる" ] },
	{"question":"額", "answers":[ "ガク", "ひたい", "ぬか", "ぬかずく" ] },
	{"question":"職", "answers":[ "ショク", "シキ", "トク", "つかさ", "つかさどる", "つとめ" ] },
	{"question":"織", "answers":[ "シキ", "おる", "ショク", "シ" ] },
	{"question":"簡", "answers":[ "カン", "ケン", "えらぶ", "ふだ" ] },
	{"question":"難", "answers":[ "ナン", "むずかしい", "かたい", "ダ", "ダン", "ナ", "にくい", "むつかしい" ] },
	{"question":"臨", "answers":[ "リン", "のぞむ" ] },
	{"question":"鎖", "answers":[ "サ", "くさり", "さす", "とざす" ] },
	{"question":"瞬", "answers":[ "シュン", "またたく", "しばたく", "しばたたく", "まじろぐ", "まばたく" ] },
	{"question":"騒", "answers":[ "ソウ", "さわぐ", "うれい", "ざわつく", "ぞめく" ] },
	{"question":"贈", "answers":[ "ソウ", "ゾウ", "おくる" ] },
	{"question":"闘", "answers":[ "トウ", "たたかう", "たたかい" ] },
	{"question":"離", "answers":[ "リ", "はなす", "はなれる", "レイ", "かかる", "かる", "つく", "ならぶ" ] },
	{"question":"穫", "answers":[ "カク", "かる", "とりいれる" ] },
	{"question":"騎", "answers":[ "キ", "のる" ] },
	{"question":"繕", "answers":[ "ゼン", "つくろう", "セン" ] },
	{"question":"礎", "answers":[ "ソ", "いしずえ" ] },
	{"question":"鎮", "answers":[ "チン", "しずまる", "しずめる", "テン", "おさえ" ] },
	{"question":"藩", "answers":[ "ハン", "まがき" ] },
	{"question":"覆", "answers":[ "フク", "おおう", "くつがえす", "くつがえる", "フ", "フウ" ] },
	{"question":"癖", "answers":[ "ヘキ", "くせ" ] },
	{"question":"翻", "answers":[ "ホン", "ひるがえす", "ひるがえる", "ハン" ] },
	{"question":"濫", "answers":[ "ラン", "うかべる", "みだりに", "みだれる" ] },
	{"question":"糧", "answers":[ "リョウ", "ロウ", "かて" ] },
	{"question":"襟", "answers":[ "えり", "キン", "むね" ] },
	{"question":"顕", "answers":[ "ケン", "あきらか", "あらわす", "あらわれる" ] },
	{"question":"繭", "answers":[ "まゆ", "ケン" ] },
	{"question":"懲", "answers":[ "チョウ", "こらしめる", "こらす", "こりる" ] },
	{"question":"癒", "answers":[ "ユ", "いえる", "いやす" ] },
	{"question":"顎", "answers":[ "ガク", "あご" ] },
	{"question":"鎌", "answers":[ "かま", "レン" ] },
	{"question":"韓", "answers":[ "カン", "いげた", "から" ] },
	{"question":"藤", "answers":[ "トウ", "ふじ" ] },
	{"question":"璧", "answers":[ "ヘキ", "たま" ] },
	{"question":"藍", "answers":[ "あい", "ラン" ] },
	{"question":"願", "answers":[ "ガン", "ねがう", "ねがわくは" ] },
	{"question":"鏡", "answers":[ "キョウ", "かがみ" ] },
	{"question":"識", "answers":[ "シキ", "シ", "ショク", "しる", "しるす" ] },
	{"question":"警", "answers":[ "ケイ", "キョウ", "いましめる" ] },
	{"question":"臓", "answers":[ "ゾウ", "ソウ", "はらわた" ] },
	{"question":"繰", "answers":[ "くる", "ソウ" ] },
	{"question":"爆", "answers":[ "バク", "ハク", "ホウ", "さける", "はぜる" ] },
	{"question":"霧", "answers":[ "ム", "きり", "ブ" ] },
	{"question":"麗", "answers":[ "レイ", "うるわしい", "リ", "うらら", "うららか", "つらなる", "ならぶ" ] },
	{"question":"鶏", "answers":[ "ケイ", "にわとり", "とり" ] },
	{"question":"鯨", "answers":[ "ゲイ", "くじら", "ケイ" ] },
	{"question":"髄", "answers":[ "ズイ" ] },
	{"question":"瀬", "answers":[ "せ", "ライ" ] },
	{"question":"簿", "answers":[ "ボ", "ハク", "バク", "ホ" ] },
	{"question":"韻", "answers":[ "イン", "おもむき", "ひびき" ] },
	{"question":"璽", "answers":[ "ジ", "しるし" ] },
	{"question":"藻", "answers":[ "ソウ", "も", "あや" ] },
	{"question":"覇", "answers":[ "ハ", "ハク", "はたがしら" ] },
	{"question":"譜", "answers":[ "フ", "しるす", "つづく" ] },
	{"question":"羅", "answers":[ "ラ", "あみ", "うすぎぬ", "つらなる" ] },
	{"question":"艶", "answers":[ "つや", "エン", "あでやか", "うらやむ", "なまめかしい" ] },
	{"question":"蹴", "answers":[ "シュウ", "ける", "シュク" ] },
	{"question":"麓", "answers":[ "ロク", "ふもと" ] },
	{"question":"議", "answers":[ "ギ", "はかる" ] },
	{"question":"競", "answers":[ "キョウ", "ケイ", "きそう", "せる", "きおう", "くらべる" ] },
	{"question":"護", "answers":[ "ゴ", "まもり", "まもる" ] },
	{"question":"響", "answers":[ "キョウ", "ひびく", "どよめく" ] },
	{"question":"欄", "answers":[ "ラン", "おばしま", "おり", "てすり", "わく" ] },
	{"question":"鐘", "answers":[ "ショウ", "かね", "シュ" ] },
	{"question":"譲", "answers":[ "ジョウ", "ゆずる", "せめる" ] },
	{"question":"籍", "answers":[ "セキ", "シャ", "ジャク", "しく", "ふみ", "ふむ" ] },
	{"question":"懸", "answers":[ "ケン", "かかる", "かける", "ケ", "へだたる" ] },
	{"question":"醸", "answers":[ "ジョウ", "かもす" ] },
	{"question":"騰", "answers":[ "トウ", "あがる", "のぼる" ] },
	{"question":"躍", "answers":[ "ヤク", "おどる", "テキ" ] },
	{"question":"露", "answers":[ "ロ", "ロウ", "つゆ", "あらわ", "あらわす", "あらわれる" ] },
	{"question":"顧", "answers":[ "コ", "かえりみる" ] },
	{"question":"魔", "answers":[ "マ", "バ" ] },
	{"question":"艦", "answers":[ "カン", "いくさぶね" ] },
	{"question":"鶴", "answers":[ "つる", "カク" ] },
	{"question":"驚", "answers":[ "キョウ", "おどろかす", "おどろく" ] },
	{"question":"襲", "answers":[ "シュウ", "おそう", "かさね", "かさねる", "つぐ" ] },
	{"question":"籠", "answers":[ "かご", "こもる", "ロウ", "ル", "こめる" ] },
	{"question":"鑑", "answers":[ "カン", "かんがみる", "かがみ" ] },
	{"question":"鬱", "answers":[ "ウツ", "さかん", "しげる", "ふさぐ" ] }
]
}
